Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Guys, if you hear me, we're riding on the shore.
We're almost there.
I guess that's what's going on.
Good guys IRL
Kind of cold
There you go.
The coppers.
The police station is right here.
Hi guys, how are we doing?
One block, almost there guys, almost there.
Okay, I think we made it okay
Okay, we're back guys. We're right there.
I'm back
Okay, I need a helmet
Yeah, it does go pretty fast. There we go. I'm gonna hear me. Hold on
You hear me
We're back
Those eyes the heart your fast heartbeat. Hi guys
Yeah, I think you guys are being here. Yeah, it was a little bit chilly. It was a little bit chilly. Yeah
Maybe I'll order a helmet
but I'm usually pretty good on the bike.
Not really anybody wears helmets around here.
And we have like teenagers on these bikes.
These bikes are fast, like 25 miles an hour.
Like you gotta be kind of careful with these bikes.
Okay.
What do you think guys, or some weed tonight?
I don't feel like.
I feel like having explosive diarrhea for the next few days, so maybe I will
We've got readmaps
Let's see what I can get going here. Hey, babe, so delivery
No, you're there. You're there chicks make some weed tonight. Let me see what I need to get another
Let's see
Vape pens
You mean a Mexican beef stew in a crock pot? Yum. Hey brown panda, what's in a Mexican beef stew?
It seems to me would be like beef like a is it like a spicy
spicy red broth, carrots, jalapenos.
Okay, what's that? What are the deals here?
Delivery, delivery.
So the can of cruise is 55% off.
Okay, 20% off, 40% off the entire menu.
Beef, red chili, beef, peppers, and onions.
Sounds good.
Okay, I'm thinking 55% off, thinking it was a Sativa.
I'm gonna show these a bit.
Oh my gosh.
I can get three of these.
Because you can't, what's up, CB?
Good to see ya.
I'm just trying to order some weed right now.
Add to cart.
If I get three of these, 66.
Check out.
Okay, free from motions.
Spend, let's see, apply.
$25 off, okay, good.
Okay, so the price I was getting,
Two grams. I can get three grams. There's a few dollars more
Hi guys
6287 cashless
Okay, I'm ordering it. Hey guys
Only three grams of babes
$20 of vape. They're all in ones
Good deal free gifts
Hey KZ, how are you? Hey CB thing that is
Jamie's
It's been going a little bit slow recently, but I do appreciate all you guys
Getting some weed tonight
Should be able to do it cat on cashless, but
If they need cash, I can go to the store.
Hey, babe.
Yeah, Trix is my baby babes.
What are we doing tonight, guys?
Hey, Mikey.
Oh, guys, hey, everybody.
Come on in.
Remember the fun night.
We're gonna do some readings tonight.
I'm in the habit of such a blast doing more readings.
Okay, I really this is what the channel was about. I was like, I'm gonna do a tarot channel. It turned into
cross between Jerry Springer and
Geraldo and Ricky Lake and I don't know. It was all these different talk shows. It wasn't really a tarot
I didn't think it more tarot in here. I
Want I want to teach you guys tarot. I want you guys all to know
At least the basics if you can always be able to understand or any reading you get or to read for yourself
People will feel that I would they'd be so offended if the people were like, oh why the restart? No, I always just you know
I did get you know, I
Went to the store. I wanted to start
The stream over again when I went to the store
The last dream was going a little bit slow. Let me see. I'm gonna change my title
I'll change the wacky Wednesday
Open panel
Tarot and
And cats
Okay
Hey guys, there we go I changed the title of the thing maybe some more people will come in now. Let's see. I'm trying to
Maybe not a lot of people wanted the IRL bike ride, but they'll want to see other things. So I got a packet of cigarette
11 bucks kind of expensive, huh?
But
They're not menthol either. They don't have it's non-menthol. They're cool is non-menthol
If you have these for California
It's really good though. It's a nice
Nice menthol-y taste their menthols are really good now. They've been for a few years now
Mentals are illegal.
Got the weed coming. Yes, got the weed coming. It's on the way
How are we doing guys
So yeah, it's been pretty interesting the past week
Can you stop this?
Ah, there we go.
Oh
I think that is no no
Think that is thank you for being a member. Thank you all members. I see thing that is is here
Appreciate you also welcome. You know, we had about I think about 20 new members recently. Wow
No, it's Homer Simpson's favorite favorite kind of nut
You know, the number one thing to hang out on too in this world
is your sanity.
Once you lose your sanity, you know, not much,
not much, you got some Jamie's name.
Oh, once you lose your sanity,
there's not very many places you can go anymore, you know.
Maintain that sanity, it's okay, yeah.
We're chilling with the kitties.
Feeling pretty good
Lola miss Lola her name was Lola. She was a show girl
You see there's gonna be text to me today
You know, but it's almost like less stress see if I got a text
So it's like less stress
having
Because people would come in you know, I got if they think there's no there's no threat. There's like nothing to worry about
You know, they'll back off a little I mean, I still am but they don't have to know that
Hi guys, how are you guys doing? We're having a good night
So time for a collective reading. It's for everybody in the chat
Everyone's it's the ring for everybody. So my takeout resonates if you do like a private reading or you'd like a
More detailed personal reading or it looks like a free reading. That's fine, too. I got you after this
Okay, what we got first? Ooh, okay, okay? The Empress, you know, this is the Queen of Hearts
I've heard the Empress in the deck, you know, but she's in a good mood here
This is when she's in a good mood, you know, and she's also planting things reminds me a little bit of
There's a person named
Madame Blavatsky and she would go around to go to India
She was the only woman let basically love to travel alone and she would go plant seeds and so there's
Some seeds being planted some abundance. This is the Empress, right? She's all the queens in the deck
The Empress is also card number three
It says, the Queen of Hearts is a revered ruler who loves spending time outdoors playing
croquet, using flamingos as hedgehogs, and she deeply values her garden of roses.
The Empress represents a strong, nurturing woman with power and prominence who, like
the Queen of Hearts, loves nature.
The Empress serves as a reminder to treat others with dignity and compassion, a lesson
the Queen of Hearts could stand to take the heart.
The tarot card carries a strong theme of appreciating beauty and nature. Make time to cultivate a beautiful environment for yourself, whether by
redecorating, spending time outdoors, connecting with nature, or planting your very own rose garden. Okay?
Plant a rose garden, guys.
How about this one? What's this next one?
Okay, seven of hedgehogs. So this is gonna be the seven of pentacles, okay?
The seven is the chariot.
So this is basically moving forward with your material plans.
There's some kind of successful moving forward.
It says, the seven of hedgehogs shows you're working hard
and planning carefully to set yourself up for the future.
Making decisions to the long term focus
should be your goal now.
Instant gratification is fleeting.
Focus on creating solid foundations for future success.
Yeah, so it's there's a harvest. There's a harvest that it looks like it's it's going well
It's looking like it's going well for you guys
Just keep nurturing those plants right and finally up. We have the moon card
Moon card. I love this moon card. It's a Cheshire cat because the Cheshire cat she thinks his smile is
The moon it looks like the crescent moon, but then it's turned out. It's just the Cheshire cat smile
Right, so there's illusions and look these roots run run deep. We can see like the top of that
We don't know what all that's going on down there, right?
Right down there you'll see the moon is hidden right? Where's the moon? Is it reflected? No, he's the moon. Reflective.
Is it? I'm not sure.
The moon.
The moon says...
What number is the moon?
The moon is number 18, okay?
So it says the moon. This is Alice's lost hope, and her way in the Tolgi wood, a crescent moon appears above her as slowly reveals itself to be no moon at all, but rather the Grim of the Cheshire Cat.
The moon card represents illusion, confusion, and deception.
Wow, there are a lot of that going around illusion confusion deception. That's a lot of the world, right like the confounding
Disappearing Cheshire cat things aren't always what they appear to be the moon warrants you not to take anything at face value
Now take care to listen to your instincts when evaluating situations or people because those messages will tell you what you need to know
So
Yep, the moon moon is full of illusion especially in the dark, right?
Isn't it easier to have like some illusions coming from the shadows rather than in full, you know
If you have a magic show, you need to use those little shadow places to hide and the obscured places
To create the illusion but fall the sun's out of all the lights are on and we can see everything
You can see all the strings. We can see what's really going on. So
Yeah, you're seeing one thing and then the moon's presenting one thing but
Make sure that
Reality you know what reality is presenting right?
Charisma's there. Hey, what's up Charisma? How are you?
Brian King what's up a man Brian?
the king
Brian's a cool guy
How you guys are cool you guys are freakin awesome just hanging out with me, you know
Because you know other people I don't know there's a lot of a lot of people wanted to say oh
Don't go to this person. Don't go to that person's page. I say go to everyone's go to whoever whatever wherever you're led to go
Wherever wherever you're entertained. It's I'm not trying to hold you here. I'm not trying to take
Audience way from other people. I'm here to be here and whoever wants to come can come the guy was like a we're not Logan Paul
We don't have
half a billion dollars and in a you know
What's prime prime drink?
the profits and a
Billion a million two million three million five million subscribers, you know
I'm a little tiny little two thousand like little little tiny little guppy a little tiny fish in the pond
Why am I trying to compete with sharks? Why am I trying to compete with the other guppies?
We're all trying to like survive, right? We can all be taken out by a shark someday.
If we hold together, we have a better chance of surviving than if we are all doing our own thing, and I
don't know. I want us to
come together
right now.
You know what I mean guys? You know what I mean? You know what I mean?
What why such a competition?
Twisted see what I want to think all the wonderful people here tonight
I'm here to hang out
I think that is you're making faces at me. What's that face?
Yeah, I got another couple copies
I'll see if as long as I can tonight a little bit just you know, it's time to get a little
I'm pulling cards bad boy you want a card
You're scared of sharks well
That's what you know the movie Jaws
Jaws was afraid you know Jaws is
People are afraid of Jaws too. You know, all you have to do is not go into the it's okay
Don't go into the water at certain times. Do you like a cup of cards bad boy? I got you a reading, okay?
Bad boy breeze with like some cards, okay bad boy breeze
Okay bad boy breeze so first we got this three of tea cups
This is the three of cups three of cups is like, you know celebrating Europe a cup of tea party for three people
It can also be third-party situations and someone you know a third party is being added to the situation
Three of teacups it says three of teacups suggests it's time for a party even if
his occasion is as simple as an unbirthday the card indicates it's time
to get together with friends and family for some fun and bonding I don't know
where all of you are as well you know I think there might be a betas on Cates
right now maybe people don't like me anymore who knows okay let people know
You care about the people you care about most know just how much you appreciate having them in your life
You know as good Tommy
Not much is different other than that, you know, I got I think I had good quality people here
Participating quality over quantity, right? Okay guys. Oh
You got the Emperor I just came out together you got the Emperor
It's the king of hearts Emperor all the kings in the deck and the chariot. There's Alice in the bottle
It's taking her forward as a vehicle, right?
So I don't know this this king this king of hearts
Whatever it is will help you to success. Okay. I'll read it both. Okay, so we got
the herm got the chariot
I heard the emperor is number four, okay.
And didn't we get the emperors too?
Oh no, that wasn't in the last reading.
So this is for a bad boy breeze.
You got the emperor.
Says though, maybe tempting to lose your temper,
the emperor reminds you of the importance of restraint.
Now is the time to resist acting impulsively.
Instead, make sure you take the time
to respond thoughtfully to situations
rather than reacting instinctively in ways
that you might come to regret in the long run.
So thoughtfully, right? Impulsively is like being led by your emotions, you know, people will be told things that will just get us into our emotions immediately.
You know, you want to be less impulsive, more thoughtful. Think, think, think, think things through, okay?
We have the chariot, chariot, very much a card of...
Moving forward successfully
Has a message of the chariot is clear stay the course you're the master of your own destiny now
You will overcome any obstacle in your way as long as you focus stay confident keep pushing forward towards your goal
And I really believe that
Stay confident like that's like what most people will try to do is
Still your confidence
And then when you if you're not confident about something what you're not even trying you're it'll just it'll say oh, I surrender I give up, right?
so we want to
make sure
You stay confident and
No, no matter what it is, you know remember guys horrible things happen to a lot of people
Bad things will happen to people
You just know I can get past this, you know
You know Trump has gone bankrupt, right? He's gone actually bankrupt and look at him now, right?
Yeah, I think he's in bank for twice
Okay
Doesn't matter how things look
You can always
Always make things better. Also look out for what people are telling you try and so like
People can put you in despair with your with your own thought actually they can
plant a seed a negative seed a negative thought and if you water the seed if you
put attention to the seed in your mind it will start growing it'll turn into
something even bigger just imagine like the seeds planted just imagine them
just exploding not growing don't let what people tell you unless there's a
positive see if there's a positive seed let the positives you grow hey sweet pea
Hope you liked your reading bad boy breeze
And nurture those positive seeds create a garden imagine your mind is a garden a beautiful garden
People are trying to put weeds and like poisonous plants and you know negative things Venus slide traps everywhere
You know, they're they have a part two right Tommy's Tommy are you stalking a sweet pea?
They have a purpose to the poison expensive a purpose to but maybe put those
As the perimeter, you know, as you know protecting your garden instead of like in the middle of the garden
Have all the beautiful plants protected by the you can use the negative to protect the positive
Tommy James, what are you doing? Are you harassing sweepy?
And let's see Tommy James in here anymore the guys. Yep. Yeah. Hey guys, I'll worry about my numbers
You know, you don't have to tell me oh, you're really falling off or blah blah
I know it's you know, I have less people here than it sometimes do but I
Have the right people here for the right reasons instead of like a lot of people here. Just a
So harass me and shit, right?
Let's see if I got a message from my
Other said they're packing the order
I need to call them and just check they can they can take my
Informer payment, but I mean three vapes three blackberry kush vapes
Or she'll pack it up the order
No, that's my phone. It's my phone. I do you I do have a ring doorbell, but I don't think it's plug you
You order confirmation be delivery
About $20 in fees the $25 discount comes out at about the same price it would have ding dong
Are you guys doing
Yeah
Yeah, so I just I may heard some negative stuff about you know Kate saying
Talking about my father Kate that any of your business
Kate
Back off, okay?
I'm not I never mentioned anything about any of your relatives. I never I'm not she was making fun of him from being passed away
That's sick. I
Mean yeah, I wish
Wish we'd live forever, right?
Why are you were you picking on me my father my kid and what he why are you saying things about me?
I don't know, there's a lot of people, I just hear people talking, I don't know, some people will try to upset me and the same things, people are saying this and that.
Sometimes they are saying that those things, and it's hurtful.
Hope you guys are all doing okay.
It might take a shorter night tonight. Wee comes who knows how long I'll last with one of wee comes
But hopefully guys can come up. Hopefully everyone's here. I'll show the comments on the stage. There we go
Your comment will now be on the screen
Thank you guys by the way. Oh my gosh, I'm getting yeah, I think I'm my first person that said remember remember for a
Month that's awesome
Thing that is see if you can do that if you click the dollar sign thing that is you might be able to give a member a
Milestone, you know, I want to thank thing that is for being a member. We have also 20 new members
The past couple days. Wow
That's an honor guys
Really cool
Oh thing that is well, you can post a member milestone
I don't know if you've been a member for a month or whatever, but if you you've been a member for over a month
You can do a member milestone chat
It's a shout out, but I don't know if I'm not sure if you remember.
Bita gave me one of her cool poetry. Yeah, Bita does. Yeah, and that's what I'd say. Bita,
I never, I never like, was like, more than a month how? Oh, so you just click on the,
click on where you joined, click on that, it will say member milestone, and then you can just do
a little member milestone. It'll say you've been a member for more than a month.
Yeah, well, I love oh, thank you. You see it. Yeah, thank you think remember for two months. Thank you so much thing that is
Two months guys. Wow
Awesome
So beta gave her a cool poetry. It was really good
Yes, I loved all my readings from beta and beta said she loved all the readings from me
But when she got mad at me, then she started saying oh, I mean they start doing tarot. You're a bad reader like
Thank you. Think that is awesome. Thank you for being a member for two months. Wow
Yeah, we're guys the channels going the channels going I'm pretty good
Really happy to have the membership going happy to have wonderful members. I
Think I might I might I might do a membership giveaway tonight
Oh, you know, we're not arguing, um, you know, I think she might be still kind of mad.
I've, I've never been mad at her.
I've never, I don't think I've ever said, I've never once went to her and said, beta,
why didn't she do this?
Why did you, why didn't you do this?
Right?
I don't like this part.
I never went to her, told her what to do, never, or expected her to like do what I told
her to do.
Same respects, but I don't know you can't control people what people do how they act, right?
But I had never I don't tell people what to do and I don't demand I'll make ultimatums
Thank you, Jamie. Yes, you are home you're home
This is a place where you can be yourself
Let me see what happens to my order.
I need to call these people here for a second.
Oh goodness gracious, I don't have my order.
Can't keep track of some of this thing that you're playing I like all the new decks
Well, I don't know it's like we're not really playing but it's like the same time we understand this is like that
you know
YouTube is not a hundred percent serious, but I
Don't play so let me see order online
Let me just see if I got my word, or I'll be right back at it. No, don't feel bad.
Don't feel bad. I'll be right back guys. I just called chicken my order.
It's okay. Don't worry.
Call me as he's like. Oh, yes, sir. Your your orders rushing to you
Thank you, don't feel bad, you know
No, no, no, it's okay sweepy because you know what if we're really friends it will work out it will work out, right?
if we're not then I
Don't know but I don't I don't know why she's so mad at me
I know I know there's been the controversial stuff people have said stuff on my show about her
She always said things about me on her show and in her chat and the it aren't very nice and you know
And it's not a big deal I sweepy the dogs barking
Got this. I think I'm going to put my big mac in the oven for a few minutes.
What do you think? How's the best way to reheat a big mac? It's just room temperature.
It's very tasty though.
Yeah, I tend to say all the wrong things. Do all the wrong things.
Very flawed human. I'm a very flawed human being, but you know what?
Have a good heart you never harm anybody
Only person I really harm does myself pretty much self sabotaging sometimes
I'm gonna come up here Lola you want to say hi to the chat Lola's just oh you're shilling. Oh
You're in a bad mood be a bad mood look at that's you it's you beautiful
Oh, what are you doing?
You clean here you're cleaning yourself. Are you cleaning yourself?
Good kitty the best cats
Hi guys, good to see you guys. Thank you all for being here. That's miss Lola
Her name was Lola. She was a show girl
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da
thank you easy for helping me get these cards
you've been there huh jammy we'll do a couple huge cards we'll see we'll see how it feels
i'd love these cards i'd love these cards though there we go collective yeah we're doing
Let's see what three card collected with the hoodu cards
There's my cards in the pop it up. Oh, it's this oh right here. Oh that one. Okay
This one's called the free man. Oh, I like this the free man
The free man right there number zero it is the
Fool card right fool is a free man, right? Why is the fool the free man?
Well
Fool has no obligate. He has no financial obligations. He has no
obligations to anybody actually he's
Is a free agent and see this guy. There's a free man
It's in front of the but a tomb. He's gonna be from a tomb. I don't know if you come back to the dead
Free man
It says here's the here's the
The Bible court says and you will know the truth and the truth will set you free John 8
32. The plant is Jimsonweed. It says the man is walking away from the tomb of Joshua John Ward of Georgetown County, South Carolina.
Ward was called the largest American slaveholder, dubbed the king of rice planters.
The man is carrying a mason jar filled with dirt. Who is this young man?
Does he know Ward personally? Why did he risk being persecuted for trespassing or witchcraft?
Does he have a purpose or all or is the man just plain crazy?
Freedom, is it a state of mind, a state of being, or is it both?
The free man doesn't think about it any more than a fish contemplates water.
The free man isn't deep because depth by definition prohibits unrestricted movement upon the surface.
The free man was probably deep prior to the outset of his journey into the unknown, the
unfathomable, the unpredictable, or he wouldn't have the wisdom to know that the concept of
safety is an illusion anyway.
had no life at all because they were afraid to take a few risks. He heard many people say
one day regarding their dreams and heard two few todays. He has conversed with talented acquaintances
that felt more comfortable dwelling on abstractions and distractions than investing in their potential.
The free man is tired of being so deep, so calculating, so restricted, so dead.
The free man is zero because zero is not a natural number, since most people normally
don't start counting with zero.
Likewise, the free man doesn't count in situations that demand subservience to conventional wisdom
or to the saddest quote.
The free man is on a whole other level because he genuinely feels that common sense is for
common people.
He doesn't think he's better than anyone, he's just accepted that new grass doesn't
grow as lusciously on a beaten path.
who encounter him, because he seems so reckless and immature, but such assessments are only
relevant when gain or loss is their focus.
The free man doesn't exist in the space where those thoughts flourish, he's more interested
in attainment of wisdom by following his passions, and when he knows to be true, whatever that
The free man has what every great ruler has always had, the courage to follow their calling
despite the possibility of dire consequences and an unshakable faith that made the courage
possible.
You receive the free man during a reading, consider the following.
What is the best thing that happened if things go your way?
What is the worst thing that happened if they don't?
Can you live without ever knowing?
Have you received an opportunity that you fantasized but were afraid to take?
Are you really that deep or are you really a free spirit or are you just a jerk or rebel without a cause?
Have you considered the financial or emotional cost of attaining that goal?
Doesn't matter whether you like surprises. They're on the way
Are you really as innocent as you profess to be as lingering self-doubt caused you boredom into satisfaction?
The new guy gal situation isn't what they appear to be maybe you need to loosen up. Let's go crazy
Let's go nuts. Are you living in the present and follow your bliss? I
like that card a lot that is like the
You know the fool car, you know people people will call people fools, right? Oh
That person they did it something stupid that they're fooled that they're they're reckless, whatever. Maybe the fool is a little bit
Less
That's bad or this this evil than people think right?
The fools is following their bliss
River it may take them
Hey, babe, I heard a dog barking there's a dog barking outside
How are we guys doing tonight?
I don't know. I haven't got a message from the weed guy yet
Don't know if they're whose dog. It's the neighbors and the neighbors doggy doggy
Yep
It looks like a looks like a powerful dog though it looks like a scary kind of dog
Hey flirty hey guys keep flirty
Florida if you want to come join the panel
Yeah, everybody come on join the panel. I don't know if I pinned it yet. It's a little puppy, huh?
Flirty what's going on with raging demon I hear hearing stories
It's okay, you don't have to tell me
This cute because you didn't as cute and I don't whatever whatever I do not have any judgments
So look what 48 views hey guys, can you can you go ahead 148 views three likes?
Only three people like me three people out of 148. That's not very good at odds
Okay, there's my I didn't pin it yet. There's my link
It's finished a movie what do you see and you watch it with uh, we have 40 demon and raging diamond
Raging diamond authority demon it's alike. Thank you. Oh, you're watching it together
Would you watch?
Sinners, ooh
Sounds good. It's for movie
Maybe watch Titanic some night, I like Titanic too
And I know some people will be like oh
You know
I'll flirt raising demons in you for your diamond. Oh my gosh, you know everyone's up in arms. I
Don't you guys are happy?
It was the whole movie not the regular Titanic
Yeah, but I'm saying you should watch Titanic Titanic's a good a good movie
You know, we should be less judgmental of people. You know anybody whoever they love. Let's go. Hey prairie. How are you page page my sweetheart?
Here's guys you ever seen page on the here's her banner. She's on the right. That's her right there
Some angels page I got like 20 new subscriptions past a couple days you got home from work
page is a
You're a caddy, but I think Paige is a caddy. I'm a golf course. I
Think Paige is the most I suppose popular person in the golf course
Why am I not a ma anymore did I do something wrong, honey? Yes Paige you're very bad. You're very very bad
Yeah, nobody's a mod but you know page page kind of
Thank you page. Yeah
Page made me a modern her chat. I had to make page a model my chat. It's only fair
Yeah, I need to have a few a few mods
Because I can't really get to the
the chat as often
But page is a good mod page. You're hired
No, and if you know him really wants to be a mod. I'll probably will consider it
It's just I need to start at ground zero and you make sure I trust everybody's they come through
Whatever floor you don't say page so is your ex-baby daddy. Yeah
Yeah, cuz uh, yeah, there was some stuff said in the chat when I fell asleep that maybe I wasn't able to get
There's any dog scene. I'll try not to fall asleep though, but I have been kind of kind of a
Getting a little bit tired lately, you know
There's someone on piano. I'll just have them up today. We had Nick up. He was doing some yard work
We watched Nick see a little yard work today. Oh
Thank You Christine. Thank you
Yeah, I got people guys. I got people watching out for this for this chat in the panel and so but I think I was okay
With the panel I left last night. It was it was Paige. It was who was here. It was Paige and
A Chris K. I don't there's another person. Maybe
Not exactly sure but hey guys are building back up with 24 people
Let's say hello to Isaiah
That was quicker than I expected. Sorry. It's a little dark in here
You're in your dungeon. Oh, you're in your car
Give your shirt on
shirt is on
It is fucking hot here
It's hot. Yeah, a lot of people I talked to
I'll talk to today said it was it was really hot. You know, I think I talked to you know, Christine and
Who else untrackable they said it was over 100 degrees. How's the weather over there? You know, um, we didn't break a hundred this week
It's been around bounce around like
90 like a high 80s to like 90 to 94, but it's super summer
So yeah, that's what I heard from untrackable, too. I wonder if you're in the same neck of the woods or he said it was
So we're we're part like the Ohio Valley when you look on a map. I mean, I don't care. I'm Ohio
So the Ohio Valley like is where like the top of this crazy
Heat line is and it goes all the way cuts all the way down to like Mississippi
And it's just like stupid fucking hot stupid fucking humid and then it's gonna breathe all these crazy thunderstorms
No, I'm sure it's off
Oh my god, sorry. Yeah, you can't see
it's all right a little dark in here guys guys just please tell them like you can't see me right
it is hot yeah uh but that's like it's gonna breed a bunch like there was tornadoes and shit
in the south today it's just gonna keep breeding this weird shit and we're supposed to have like
it was supposed to be like torrential fucking down pouring today to start for the next four days but
Zero rain came in now the rains tomorrow night, maybe
But yeah, it's just it sucks fucking sucks
How's your night going?
um, it's not bad, and I did a nice nap today, and I
Mean my show has been actually going actually since I have had less people in the show and less drama and actually been
Doing more readings and you know have had more members and so it's like I think we you know
It actually it doesn't matter the number doesn't matter
It's like if you have quality people in your chat
They you know actually people that fuck with you that actually like like you and instead of I have had a bunch of haters in the chat
The haters just kind of distracts from everything and
Quality over quantity man. Yeah, so I'm happy with 25
quality
Yep
So yeah summer summer and diamond you want to come up here and chat. I think that you guys should be fine
I think that uh, what's up summer? What's up diamond? Hey? Yeah, we chatted. Are you chatted? Yeah?
Yeah, I sort of make sure we work out all I don't think so. I don't think there's any issues with diamond in summer, but
Diamond or is everything cool? I don't know if you diamond is now diamonds dating raging demon now. You can't go up right now
Okay, come up soon, but you know let's summer know that you know everything's cool. I
Forgot which one raging is I've encountered him before
Well, I don't know if diamond can't she's they can't go up right now, but
Hopefully well guys this is the place to work things out to have a to have a chat about things to
To really, you know, this is not gonna be like, you know, just biting calling names
It's gonna be you know working things out you posted videos today. Diamond. What were the videos?
What?
I was gonna say you want to do a reading for me. I'm super curious cuz all right, so
Beeta gave me a reading the other night
Emma had you Emma gave me a reading to that was very scarily similar in ways to beat us
So I'm curious if yours comes out similar
Okay, let's have a look not that I'm comparing and contrasting because no, no, no, no again. Yeah, we're all we're all different readers
That guy is great to get
Different opinions from different readers come out similar then if shit's gonna be weird
Although, I mean, it is theoretically, if you believe it, the heart of my card, so it should all come out very similar.
Okay. Well, okay, so I see you've been spending some time alone right now.
You've been like really like, you know, the hermit card.
So you've been, you know, it's taken, you kind of like took yourself out a lot of situations and been on your own thinking about things.
And I also see there's been some kind of like a really big sadness lately here first page coming up
You've experienced some sadness some regrets. It's I'm uh, some tears. Hi page
We're doing great
No, no, no, no, no, no worries. I'm just I'm my third car
Then you got this
I said finally finally we got finally got the queen of queen of flowers and this is she's a rose right this is the queen of
Yeah, she's the she's the rose that queen of the rose queen in the garden Alice in Wonderland
I think I believe flowers are the wands
Queen of flowers. This is I don't know. This is maybe a woman in your future or
Someone here to help you
It says the queen of flowers says
The queen of flowers is a social person who takes pride in her appearance and speaks her mind with elegance and authority
Admired by others she commands attention wherever she goes
It's time to hold your head up high put your enviable talents and skills on display and embrace the unique traits that make you who you really are
Okay
Well, that's a mess. Oh, yeah, but that's I think that maybe that's why it's the queen because I think maybe there's a queen in your in your future with those qualities maybe and
I'm thinking it's like a woman you're gonna meet or some kind of she's really fiery and
But she has a thorn
Well, you know the Queen the Queens the Pages the Kings and you know those are usually
Represent some people in your life, you know, so if it's not yourself
It's another person and I that was in the future position
So I think you've been spending time in solitude
You've had some heartbreak and there's gonna be some I got a woman that will bring you out of this
I think with these qualities that I got maybe look for a fire sign
I can't see right now I love you all and be like a personal shout out don't be lame about it. Hi, stay chair. What's up? I can't see I can't see champ so I can't see right now I can't see right now I can't see right now I can't see right now I can't see right now I can't see right now I can't see right now I can't see right now I can't see right now I can't see right now I can't see right now I can't see right now I can't see right now I can't see right now I can't see right now I can't see right now I can't see right now I can't see right now I can't see right now I can't see right now I can't see right now I can't see right now I can't see right now I can't see right now I can't see right now I can't see right now I can't see right now I can't see right now I can't see right now I can't see right now
Yeah, so I'm safe. I'm safely driving my vehicle right now. Not looking at you. I'm not. I just got home for work and I don't like going into my house until I'm ready to you because it's sad in there. So I just sit out here for a little bit. Oh, fair enough. I mean, just burn it down. Yeah, okay.
Yeah, I thought about it. I thought about it.
Yeah.
Yeah. What's what's about to keep you from doing it?
I need a boot to fit in it for a little bit.
I guess.
I don't know. Oh, no. Yeah.
Thank you, psyche for catching.
You're welcome. I don't know. I
see. I see Christine. Christine.
Christine Summer and 30 Diamond. You know, it's like 30. I don't quite agree with
like you're you're kind of using some incorrect terminology.
You know, we should all respect one another and it's like, you know, are you doing
Summer come in because we can have an outnumbered female panel at this point
Well, I know psyche that's not psyche stream, but you know
Yeah, it's a little bit of controversy
So someone wants to come up and explain this about home balances are you doing for you?
So no, oh, yeah, yeah, I'll pull a card and I don't know if Paige has her cars
But I'll certainly pull a car for you. Oh here
Okay girls
Really girls really aren't fighting we have
a man who seems to think, well, no, it's not a man.
It's not a man.
It's just somebody with penis who thinks it's okay going
after people and making lies up and it's getting thickening.
Well, I know I didn't I just didn't agree with yesterday because I was you know
I was reading the chat and then
She kind of use it in an appropriate term referring to someone on the panel and you know
We don't need to refer to resort to name-calling. Well, here's the problem
Mr. Price. Yeah, um, I was in a chat today
Diamond decided to lie and say I said something where two months went back and checked my activity until diamond
I did not say anything and in turn
She is calling me a dog. She is putting Miguel's
messages up and we know Miguel
You shouldn't be treating anybody like that, and you know better.
Oh wait a minute, because we're not, we're not, like, there's all kinds of situations.
Because I don't even know, I didn't even know what the fuck was going on today,
and somehow I'm throwing in all this bullshit.
I ain't even been fucking around.
I don't even know what's going on still. I might just jump. I might just jump down. No, you're fine. You're fine
That's what I'm here to talk about
30 diamond you're wrong Nicole went through and
He man and all
Shit me and Christine have been cool with a flirting diamond. We lost our beef
We we sit there and
And then I guess that all this something said some shit
I don't know I don't fucking know cuz I wasn't even there
I woke up to fucking some tag bullshit and it's bitch. What's the play fucking eggs?
So she wants content I'll give a fucking content because we squashed our fucking beat
She's been on my panel and everything. I said, not right now. Hold on a second, please.
She's been on my panel and everything. There was no fucking issues. And now
she's got all kinds of shit going on with everybody else and somehow me and Christine's being fucking thrown in it.
This please.
And um,
T-Man nor I called you a predator, but
after listening for the last two days, you appear to be a predator.
Where's the clip, bitch? Where's the clip? No, bitch. I don't call you a predator. I call you a fucking man.
a predator so where's the fucking clip that i called you a predator and i
called you shit in weeks
what the fuck are you talking about
i don't use the word predator but i call you a man
i love you psyche i'm peace now too
Nobody called her a predator other than the people who she's been giving out her messages to
Well
He shouldn't be showing pictures that were privately sent to him. He shouldn't be bringing Miguel into this at all
Right, well, she does she takes advantage of people dude, and then she fucking sit there and try to make them look some type of way
She's a weird fuck. He's a weird fucking wave lip-dick little bitch
And why are you at it bitch?
Why don't you fix your fucking stomach cut because we all see how you look on when you're posting your fucking pictures on the track, bitch
fix your goddamn self
Take some more steroids and tighten that fucking belly up bitch
She's lame as fuck. She's lame as fuck. So it's okay. She ain't gotta come up on panel right now
I'll get that bitch and DJ keep talking and I'm gonna get your ass, too
And I see you on panel, too, bitch
Who do you think with the drama was too psyche, you know me and her don't get along
And what happened to you in a lecture I never noticed that
She's fake that's why
Well, let me see. I don't know what like a I'm not sure that the the the details of this thing is that I think I think think you know
There's somebody's name should be left out of this and somebody should not
Even if her Christie were arguing why the fuck are you bringing Miguel in this bullshit? Why are you bringing me in your bullshit?
They got nothing to do with me
And the answer I got none go Miguel we fucking she knows that he's got fucking issues. Hey, what the fuck are you doing bitch?
Yeah, well, I just didn't like the cat some of the language that was used like you know referring to him and
By her and you know a woman you're a man remember that diamond remember that bitch
I'm a natural born fucking woman in your man. There's your content bitch
I did not call you a predator and if I did it has nothing to do with Miguel and
or
summer
Nothing
You're fucking weird you're lame as fuck
He's right man in situation, and then you release all the bullshit and then you want to start making a drama cuz you're just a nuts bitch
And any you fucking dudes they go backstage or go in private conversations with this bitch y'all fucking stupid
I'll be right back guys. You guys talk for a second. I have to get my weed. It says that once again
He's been waiting for it
Clearly this bitch is gonna show all your shit. I would not fucking go in fucking private conversation with this bitch
Bitch, who's gotta be jealous? You ain't never gotta be jealous of you, bitch!
You take a pill to try to be like me, remember that?
The fuck?
You have shown a lot of private stuff that were sent to you specifically
You're putting it out there to try to humiliate you're trying to humiliate raging. You're trying to humiliate Miguel
You can tell she's not involved in the trans community because she's doing shit that like are you fucking kidding me?
It's shit like this that puts people at fucking risk. She's a lame fuck. He's a lame fucking bitch
I've said it before and I'll say it again, bitch you need to get connected with some people around because what you're doing is going to get yourself fucking hurt one of these days, you dummy.
Or sorry, I mean, we can tell all of flirty does he lies. He deceives people and it's ridiculous.
Fucking flabby flat ass. It's your fucking ass a belly bitch
Okay, but she's wants to start he want he wants to start it, but she doesn't want to take
Somewhere I'll get the bitch
She's sitting comments. She can play a little fucking games right now. That's fine
Nasty ass fucking bitch
Like I said, she's gonna keep doing a shit to be straight men and keep doing and trying to humiliate them a shit and
She's gonna get herself fucking hurt one day. She's fucking dumb
And you fucking men need to stop talking to this bitch behind the scenes and they and be shocked where she shares your shit like what the fucking stop
Or don't have your shit exposed cuz you gonna do it
And everybody's gonna talk about it because that's what she wants she wants content
Well
Yes, he he just wants content
Apollo I have been here all day. They're just back off
I kick you off the panel
And go be no more panel
He decided to lie and he's got private messages of Miguel up.
He decided to start trouble and started showing all private messages and actually actually
what really started it besides the problem is he manipulated him and made him think that
When I'm talking my shoulder messes, I'm talking about other shit.
Miguel messes are very fucking, you know what I mean?
Innocent compared to some of the others that she keeps in her phone.
Well, but she shouldn't be taking advantage of somebody in Miguel's situation.
Of course she does. She thought she was going to get a lick.
She thought she was going to get a lick out of Miguel.
And she sat there and played with him and they think that she was you know, I'm saying like he thought about she was a fucking woman
He didn't think she was a man. I
Yeah, I understand what you're saying, but um psych recognized there is an issue and he said come up and talk about it
Yep, sure did here we are
Psych also knows that there's been an issue for the last two days with diamond he has been wreaking havoc in
several communities
I
Yeah, she's got a home
She every single time dude. She's just there does that shit
She gets all these fucking straight guys gets whatever they got going on in private conversations, and she fucking exposes it
Hi guys back. I'll come back. Did you get what you needed?
Doesn't lead
Anybody talking about anything I wouldn't came up here with this if psyche didn't say come up here and talk about it
So you don't like to take it up with him
Would you like I would like you guys to be able to work things out, but I know
Yeah, but we were hot. That's the thing. I had no idea we had an issue until she tagged me when she thinks this video
I don't give a fuck about the video. I stand on every fucking leg
I say no matter what and one thing when people get to know me though realize I really don't give a fuck
So it's the fact that if she thinks that her and Christine
I don't know if her and Christine got into it
I know Christine was super five busy fucking today
So I don't know Christine said that it wasn't her she didn't get into it where so I believe her so it wasn't all
You know, but either way you supposedly get into it with Christine
And then you pull me and Miguel in your bullshit and like again all of us were fine included her and Christine
As far as I know sure and and I didn't I she said
Diamond said that I called him a predator, which I did not.
Two of the moths went back and looked at my activity,
and I have it on screenshot that they said, no, I did not.
So Diamond was trying to deflect on what she was doing to Rageon Demon
and Bita and Kate and all these people.
Well, I don't either I ask a couple of questions and then instead of her going after the people that have been going after her for the last two days
She chooses to put Miguel's private messages up
right and
You know, it's a little bit inappropriate. I would say, you know
First of all, it's private message
It's special. I'm going to do it any of this. He ain't got nothing to do with this the rage and demon and all that
Whatever's going on all that, you know what I mean? Like why put him in all that? That's I'm not upset about anything
She tagged me and I'm more pissed off like dude, you know that he's like special. What are you doing? Why are you doing this?
I mean it's like it is kind of a low blow to you know
I don't I don't think he he he had any intentions other than you know, he likes somebody
No, he did he thought she was a girl and he was like ooh booby's like oh, okay cool
Someone's like, you know, give me attention. Let's talk like, you know, whatever and she took full advantage of that
But we all know that because that happened, but you know what a month or almost two months ago
It all that shit's been dead and because her and all these people with the hard rage and whatever's going on with that situation
And all the other people that's involved in it. You're gonna I wake up to being tagged in and again
I don't give a fuck about me the tag. Why are you putting Miguel shit out there again?
Yeah, she's building her brand so she has to get all these straight men and
Expose them as he says because she's building her brand. She think
Her brand is of something and it doesn't matter
the destruction that he is causing to other people.
Well, you know what?
The crazy thing is though,
and I think it's like he can even agree with me.
Doing shit like that can eventually get you
seriously fucking hurt.
Yeah, well, that's why I did tell Florida Diamond
I was like, I don't think you should be.
Out on this out doing anything on the street
I think everything should be virtual because we live at a day and age where you can just make even more money
sitting me on a webcam and safety then
Putting yourself in danger situation the street where somebody might feel fooled or not
Yeah, yeah, I mean that that and that's a great point too, but I was more so talking about just like, you know
I mean you want to you want to I guess she has a thing where she wants to expose straight guys or whatever, right?
But like that in itself you ain't gotta be walking no track to get hurt by that
You know, I mean you I mean you humiliate. I mean we all remember when what was it?
Jenny Jones or whatever when that one guy went and told the other guy secretly that he loved him
And then they went home and he killed them because he felt embarrassed. Yeah
There's been a lot of cases of that. Yeah
100 millions of cases thousands of cases since that happened right because that was back in the Jones day
You know what I mean? And it's like dude you're doing this shit and it's fun
It's content and it's drama for everybody on the internet
But in real life, you're gonna fucking hurt one you're gonna fuck with one of these guys and you're gonna humiliate them
And they're gonna come and they're gonna fucking hurt you. What do you do it?
And if anybody watched Raging Demon today, he was out of his mind.
I mean, he was acting like somebody I've never seen act and it's all because of what
Flirty Diamonds is doing.
Yeah, but I mean sort of that was just insane that that she was just on the phone with demon. They were watching a movie called
Yeah, I know but it sounds like I mean I know they were on you know
Bita was talking to diamond in a night and then he was on the on the line with diamond, you know
And but it's like it's no it's a judgment against anybody
And I we you know it you know everyone has said this if they find love that's fine, but
He went around it the wrong way. It's like he's using all these straight men as
Marks on their belt to to see how many they can how many they can get
I don't know what's going on with the other situation because I've been busy. I've been I've barely been around, you know what I mean
But I will say like my thing is again, I'm gonna continue to go back to the Miguel thing
What the fuck does Miguel have to why are you posting his shit? What what does he have to do with any of this?
Because I've been around he only came up the other night when he was a panel with all of us because you know
It was chill and we're up here. Just you know, it was chill
But he hasn't even been around why I post his stuff
What does he have to do with any of the he don't have none to do with Christine?
He has none to do with the people that are attacking her or Rage and Demon or whatever
I don't even know if they're getting attacked. I just I know there's some shit going on
It has nothing to do with that
So diamond says like I said people want to use Miguel and rage he's the same shit
I'm not sure I understand but you know Miguel Miguel is this you know when I Miguel comes on
He's just like he's happiness. He's he's innocence. He's like, you know, he just has a good heart
He doesn't have bad intentions for anybody. You might understand everything that's going on like you know, but he's
Yeah
I'm not comparing the only part I'm I don't know what's going on rage and demon and and diamond
I don't give a shit to be honest with you something really none of my fucker business to have with it my thing is
Miguel has nothing
To do with this we watch I have nothing to do with this
Far as I knew everything was cool. And again tag me and whatever you want bitch. I don't give a fuck about that
Why Miguel?
Marty Miguel has not said two words to you. Miguel is not responsible for what other
People are saying and doing why do you want to do this to Miguel?
because other people
Miguel has nothing to do with it
Right
Miguel has nothing to do with whatever is going on with the whole rage and shit which I again
I don't even know what the fuck is going on with it nor do I give a shit what's going on
It's gonna say me to fucking brain cells not to know what's on going on with it
But one thing I do know is Miguel has nothing to do with it
So what is she talking about when she's saying so once people stop using that shit for him from him when I never
Want to use him? I'll drop it, but I won't stop the tree from being out
Keep the video up all you want take Miguel shit down
Yeah
Do whatever you want with me. I don't give a fuck bitch. I can handle it
Leave him. I mean
Take the girl shit down. Yeah, I don't have to agree and I know Christine. Yeah, you agree Christine
Like it's like he to leave him out of it. This is like this take his name. This don't involve him
It's like he doesn't need to be confused by that
No, but flirty seems to be trying to drag everybody and anybody into it. That's what he's doing
Tag me clip videos make videos of me kissing bitches. I don't give a fuck dude. I don't care like right at the end of the day
I really don't you're not an ass motherfucker that I give two fucks about
But Miguel has nothing to do with anything
He's not in this community. He don't even know what the fuck is going on and you're just like for what for what?
Oh
All people should be doing with Miguel is like cheering him on to do his Coney Island IRL streams and no
Until you tagged me no one's even mentioned Miguel. What are you talking about?
Yeah, diamond what no, no, why bring it up what diamond why why bring why put him into it
Why bring him up or you know, it was very whatever happened
That was squashed months ago. Yeah, like you know my panel and everything like we've been cool
This is what I woke up today, and I was like I was like, I'm gonna tag me
I thought she was tagging me and something like hey, I'm gonna do a panel or you know cuz we've been cool
So when I woke up and I see all this bullshit on I was like when I see all this bullshit
I was like wait a minute. What the fuck is going on?
So because of other people that he has no control over you want to try to humiliate him perfect example
Miguel never showed a dick pic never
Miguel is a guy from another community. He's he's a special needs dude. He's fucking amazing. We all have a Miguel's a sweetheart
He and diamond were like chat or whatever
He was he thought diamond was a woman. So he was like, you know, oh my god, this lady likes me
You know what I mean? Like he didn't know now in in diamonds and this is what I don't understand in diamonds
Like being there was a couple times she tried to be like, hey, you know like Miguel
I'm not really a woman and it took like a lady coming up and speaking in Spanish
You know what I mean to kind of explain to him like what was going on. So all that got worked out
That's why I don't understand what the fuck she's doing right now
Yep
Man Eric's in the chat. She said Miguel wouldn't do that stay turn. So what's up a minute?
I know Miguel is he has been told multiple times from women in that community. Okay. Well, I know
That's because he's got an adult body
but
Boys
Okay, so like
We're not gonna do this. We're not gonna make this about Miguel has done that wrong. Yeah. Yeah
No, we're not doing any that Miguel's done nothing wrong. He hasn't even been around in months
Right
I didn't know anything about any of this until yesterday. So what's been going on for seven days?
I haven't even known I asked questions
Last last evening to find out what's going on and then today I asked a couple of questions
Okay, but filthy flirty diamond you said
For almost seven days, but if other people diamond are sitting here saying shit that are just boasting you and shit
What does that have to do with Miguel and what the fuck does that have to do with me or Christine for that matter if we're not
The one saying it and Miguel's not saying it then why on the fuck are you throwing any of us in your bullshit?
That doesn't make sense
Yeah, what did I run what could I have possibly said today that a hundred other people watching didn't
This week, shit, oh, because other people, and Christine,
because Christine and other people were supposed to be today,
this is what I decided to wake up and do.
Again, tag me or whatever you want, bitch,
I don't give a fuck.
You want content, I'll give it to you.
Why are you fucking with me, get off.
Um, I haven't I have not been in there and you know, I don't go tough sand man's or Kate's that
Thank you Phillips
And if they've been spreading the narrative you fueled the fire not me
But again, that's all but notice is that's 40 diamonds Christine and he meant there's no Miguel or summer in that
Because the bitch was sleeping I was knocked the fuck out and I don't know what the fuck Miguel was doing
But I know he wasn't in this conversation. I have the screenshots from today
I'd like the screenshots from flirty diamond that I called him a predator because I did not
So where do you got screenshots where the no, I do where I didn't
Amanda I'm talking to plenty diamond. I'm talking me and her gone back and forth right now
I don't care. I don't understand what the fuck she's doing right now. I don't care. What? Oh, and then the 30 30
Okay, so I'll say remember I remember when Miguel met flirty like you know flirty was argue with Michael
Like was the mono on my panel and then Miguel Miguel came up and he's like hey
He's like leave my even leave that girl alone like leave that and then Miguel really thought she was a woman
He didn't realize that that flirty had a penis until a friend of his
who spoke Spanish to him. He didn't even understand the word transvestite or flirty trying to put
transvestite in Hispanic. He did not understand it. He had no clue what a transvestite was until
Okay
From this community, but yeah, I do remember that night too. We're all trying to explain just to make sure that he understood
Oh, I deleted my messages perfect you and then I guess you have a screenshot of me calling you a predator
Perfect showing
If not, you're lying
Don't remember ever like, you know, I remember like remember the message were shown to show that she's like he said
Oh, let me fly over to New York and she and she was like. Oh, no, it's we just it's too soon
We just met so that I never saw anything asking for any money. So it's Miguel. Okay, first of all, Miguel
He has a caregiver who handles all
He doesn't
It was it's already been squashed
Like you're rehiring some shit on a special needs dude like this is really fucking like this is so fucking low ball like like really dude
Like all the other fucking people all the other fucking in this community
You could be going back and forth with right now
We could be me and you could be talking to the best what you want, but if you want content you want to argue come on, baby
I got you
Wait a minute. It's stupid to even be having this fucking oh if he had money with airplane fuck all that that shit was squashed
He has nothing to do with any of the shit that is going on right now
And so these conversations of trying to justify or prove or fuck all that it was already squashed
Sorry, go ahead Christine go after the people who have been having lives
Surrounding you and raising demons go after those people
What a concept go after the true ones if you feel you're a victim, but you're not
Right
Yeah, good fight with the people that are fighting you like you'll pick on someone your own size
You know
I think I think it's something
A hundred people in there today
criticizing flirty diamond and he decides to say I called him a predator which I did not
Like Thompson about the go like if I can wait something
You like making issues out of this it
Yeah, you really
Like I don't know humiliating straight news or some shit. I don't know what the fuck that's weird
But you got something going on there attention seeking for his land
All it is he even did he even said it he was telling Shannon that last night. He was laughing about everything. He's done
You know
Because he's gonna come across one motherfucker whether it be on the Internet or whether it be in quote-unquote real life
And you gonna try to humiliate that motherfucker that motherfucker go for your range all fucking lifestyle
So you really need to check note on that girl
My real shit you you setting yourself up for failure
Why do you think you clouding everybody else in the long run when that horse bites? I'm a fucking go buy harm
I'm jumping down. I gotta go to bed. Thank you. What's in 30 diamond?
Get over yourself. I don't give a fuck what you did with Rick
I don't know what you did with him. I don't give a fuck what you did with him
You just cloud you you a fucking joke dog like pearl you you live as far
It's clear so you keep it keep whatever you want to tag me whatever you want
It's I don't give a fuck. I got smoke for you every time I see you and I'm gonna catch you on the panel
I promise you that
Well
Until then go do you
Wow, well
You know, maybe these
Maybe talking through these things. Maybe you know conflict sometimes arise so we can discuss them and come to better understandings
Hopefully we can like come to understandings and
Be friends. Oh, we have I say it back to had a summer home. It's a good summer
Go back back to the garage. I'm back in the garage. Fuck. Yeah
Give AC in your garage at least
Today and it was a hundred none
Bro, you're you're so smart cuz like I just looked over and there's a window AC unit granted
It's not gonna cool the whole fucking garage, but like
We might watch this fucking happen, I don't know if I got sealers you should try to make it happen like real
So at least I think the you know I'm saying that they hit off of it. Yeah
When you're right, I am into good news today
Damn, all right. All right. I'm not just drama. I didn't give good advice. I'm out
I'm gonna go to bed those gonna be an issue because I know I'm gonna get cussed out in the morning about the electric bill
Well just cut it off when you know what I'm saying when you go back upstairs and then you know we won't be here.
I'm gonna have to try and remember.
Hey that's the problem.
Well if I'm still around I'll be like, cut this one off.
So I can tell him to cut it off when he goes to bed.
He'll probably be, he'll be up.
Alright where's it going though?
You're the runner. You're the track star because your ass is in chat. You're gonna bring your ass up on chat
But it's okay like I said, I'll catch you and if you run from the panel, that's cool, too
You know whatever but you'll be you'll be somewhere. So I'll pop up. I got you
And I'm talking about channels channels channel the panel that's it
Yeah
Pretty quiet here lately. I don't I don't know why but
You know also it's been like but it's been like I've been doing more readings and like you know, there's been like cooler panels
Not not as much arguing but a lot of people just disappear. I don't know
Together I'm modded everybody and like
I know I probably we get offended if I was a modded bit
I don't know how people get offended. I mean all they gotta do is start their own page and they can be the mastermod
Yes
Yeah, and everyone can mod who they want it's like but
For your panel, you know, I mean, I said I had too many mods. There's too much going on in chat
It's gonna be too many people people would be you know set with the mods and I
Didn't want that. I just want people to feel a fun here and not worry about modding
Hold on
Good night, Christine
Yeah, Christine, good night
Make sure you take your pills, babe
Make sure you take them pills
Aw, she said good night
That was sweet
It's just a silly shit
You know what I mean, because like I said, everything was squashed
And it's like, she's the
You know what I'm saying, she's the smoker
I gotta always shoot up
Well, that's weird when conflict just arises out of nowhere over something like you know long put to put to rest. It's like
It's like yeah, dude. Like I can see like if I was talking shit. I was doing something, you know, okay cool
This is like this is oh shit. Yeah, I'm sorry. That's why it's weak
Well, yeah, I mean it I just I hope
I hope you can come up soon flirty and talk, you know
Hi Christine, what does I say to say is gone. Yeah
People better psyche. Why do these two ladies came up here?
No, they didn't come to do anything. They were responding to 40 diamond
There's been a lot of drama on the show. We are like kind of I'm phasing out a lot of like the
Yeah, I really want people to make up on this. I want people to come to an agreement.
Well, you have to psyche asses to come up on panel and talk and do whatever we need to do.
Get it out and diamonds decided to stay in the chat.
But we brought up our panel because psyche told us to come up on panel.
Asked us to come on panel. Sorry.
Yeah, what you said. I'm sorry for bitting you earlier.
I didn't know psyche told you to come up. Obviously, you know.
If that's the case, I'm totally not an asshole about it because psyche wanted it.
Yeah, I would not have brought I would not have came up here with it. I but I got my own channel
I bring you know, I'm saying that's content for my channel
But like he said I'll come up here and try to talk it out. Okay, cool. I'll do that
I just want to say though how quick and easy your solution was like it's already in it's already ready to fucking go
Let's let's try and look at that
Let's go. Oh, oh, baby. Oh, it's. Oh baby. Look, winter summer. Oh my god, summer, you are a fucking gene.
And I realized too, it's even easier because I have to turn the light switch off when I go in that controls the light that's right over my head.
And that's going to control that air conditioner also.
Oh, it's nice. It's all in the same circuit.
There you go. Well, you know now I got to kind of stand on this although I'm not complaining
I just got a switch
I got such good advice for my chat. You know, that's really cool. Like, you know, there's
a lot of people with a lot of
A lot of knowledge and there's they give me some great advice always so
That was so easy
How long has that been sitting there? You just didn't realize like
My mom it's got mold on it. I was supposed to throw it away over a month ago because my we got a new like my mom got a new one
So, uh, yeah, for a month now, it's been supposed to be it in the garbage and I never tossed it
If I take some bleach and like wipe that off because you don't want that mold like, you know
I mean, I don't give a shit. Now I'm outside in the garage. I don't give a fuck
It's outside. Nope. You know, it's, you know, no, I don't give a fuck
I don't give a shit
Maybe one day I will, uh, I'll not clean it, but uh, I mean, fuck it. Um
Phew
Maybe I can catch it earlier, yeah
and be like, hey, go get a bleach right now.
Fucking amazing.
Yeah, are you guys under that heat wave?
It was 100 and on today.
We didn't get the hundo, but we had 90 was our peak today.
96, 94 yesterday, 96 the day before.
And then it's like 100% humidity.
It's like being a fucking floor.
was 109 and 100% parking humidity I was like oh dude I am sorry that sucks where are you uh like
where do you sell southern then a little farther south yeah I'm in Kentucky oh okay oh all right
so you're right oh damn you're just right below us because that well I'm the north end Ohio I'm
Oh, yeah, you like effect up there. I mean, we got the river, but it's just you know, Kentucky's because all the mountains and stuff
We have a lot of
That crazy fucking yeah. Oh god. Yeah. No, that sucks. I wanted to move to Kentucky to Kentucky, Tennessee
Hey, so I don't know. Oh, sorry. Go ahead
No, good
I'm gonna say the only thing where I regret the like I still really want to move to Tennessee at least but like
Kentucky Tennessee area is the mountains and like all the crazy fucking weather pattern that's been going on last few years, right?
The only reason I don't want to move there cuz yeah, I mean Ohio well, although I am next to like a major lake
It's right, you know
Not throwing stone anymore. My last house was but
Still though, it's nice to find that big-ass body of water and Tennessee, Kentucky ain't got that
You know unless I'm in North Kentucky. What's up, babe?
Sorry about that
Oh psyche drop down in my place, and I know when to step down, you know, I mean, yeah
We both did
We're back we're getting
Yeah, I'm good with that
I actually had a really good day. I mean it was hot as fuck on outreach, but all in all it was a really good day
It was today was a good day
My wash machine, I'm sorry. It's really loud because it's not a high-spin right now and it shakes my whole fucking house
And so it's just can't even hear it. Yeah
Don't know what you're talking about
Yeah, but I really can't hear it though. It's not whatever your mic's not picking it up for whatever reason
Thanks a lot. Thanks
Okay, we could meet halfway in the Canadian border. All right, and then we'll just go have a fun drinking extravaganza
You can show me all around the wilderness and skinwalkers, and we can go trout fishing
Well now the wash is trying to run away
You can do it
Well, at least it ain't the dryer.
The dryer is what eats everybody's socks, though.
It's got a little monster in there.
The little fucking dryer gnomes, bro.
Man, I don't understand.
Still, that is the biggest unsolved mystery in my life.
It's like, where the fuck do the socks go?
You know what's funny, right?
Because that was like me losing your matched pairs, right?
You never fucking found them, right?
Since I got my dog, I don't have that issue.
I don't have a dryer, no I miss you. I have a fucking, alright, the holes. Like, alright, do the holes line up? Because you ate this exact pair of-
Fuck it!
Uh, and also, I can never, like, the socks I'm looking for, well, I know where to find them, they're in his cage.
So I can always find them, the socks are never missing, it's just, are they in-
Right to the motherfucker
But you know, well, I've got I got ten kids and I can tell you all throughout the years of them
They're all mostly grown my my youngest is gonna be 17 soon, but
To you man all the years of socks has gone. I'm just still
Like ever years of fuck gone
Surprisingly enough like never well, I think cuz I wore black socks mainly
You know once I had like high school and nobody else did I never really lost socks that much
They got destroyed by dogs, but especially my current dog, but I never really lost them
I don't think you know, I think theft is part of it
Yeah, but if you don't wear black socks, you only wear white you ain't stealing mine, so I
Got away with
I have all kinds of socks. I like much much almost dogs
Oh, I I just recently started doing that out of pure laziness because I got tired of digging through my socks to find a match
I mean you're mismatching black socks, right? There's a Nike logo on one and not on the other one
but
But girls can do that because you guys all have like cute really fucking
Yeah, it makes it interesting, right? You know, you mix the yellow with the fucking pink with right
Right, it's cool. Well, I have a son
I have all ankle socks, so you really can't see them in my tennis shoes, but like a little bit
so
No, mine are
Oh, mine are just normal. Like what the
Cass high cat whatever. I don't know podcast. Yeah
They might have been knee socks for a regular guy, but I have a fucking huge cat or well
large cats, so
Nah, they're just regular jocks jock, whatever cut fucking bullshit. I
Can't do the shorts no more used to do only ankle socks
But then I started wearing boots all the time and it was well ankle socks and boots do not go well
Yeah, when I were my I work
Some of the stuff I have to do and yeah, we're big our like they go up
My calf like I wear boot socks. I have actual boot socks. Oh
Shit, I didn't know boot socks were a thing
Yeah, they have like really I have nice ones they're casual here
So like they feel really good like on you when you're a theater in them
So fancy
It sounds it is
Take care of your feet like you know, so I'm really big on you know what I put on my feet
It has to be good shit. I used to be everything else lazy
Yeah, oh, you know what? I keep going to this side of my fucking I think the lighting's better
But I keep going the opposite side of the garage at the fucking air conditioners on
Actually, it's not bad over here
We just have to hold my phone. I'm gonna step down for a bit. I'll be back. Um, thank you for being here
Thank you, and sorry everybody, you know again, but site site you thank you for attempting for us to come up because last time we
Eventually talked it out and everything ended up getting squashed. So maybe we'll see what happens, but
Holler see y'all later call it squash who cares. I mean it's
Leave me at Miguel. Well, that's my only thing. You know, I mean he's a special needs guy like I just I'm not with this shit
I don't care about me. Like I'm a big girl. I can take this it but leave him alone
But anyway, I'll see y'all later. See you
Welcome back psyche. Welcome. Hello. I'll say is the room too. Oh
Yeah, all right. Oh page next age, but I guess you know
Everybody can say actually that fucking air conditioner. I can feel it over here. That's a prize. I can say page can say too
I mean we can all say yeah, I like well, I can't I don't have any stage
Well, we'll buy some sage when's all ash
I don't need another rabbit hole to go down and another fucking
Once I start learning and fucking buying and investing and shit
Then it just becomes a problem because I go very far down a rabbit hole
Well, I mean the rabbit holes are just because you're go you're like you don't have a focus
I mean if you go for the focus of learning, but it's one thing you then you go you go then you're all of a sudden
You're at the madhead or sea party and all of a sudden you're like, you know at playing croquet in the Queen's garden
And all of a sudden you're you're all these different places all these different because you're just like because there's a lot of every rabbit hole
has a whole character cast of characters a whole bunch of things to learn and so
You know, it's like you have to like, you know, just be happy going on the rabbit holes.
No, you'll eventually come out of the rabbit holes or
You get lost in the rabbit hole, but that's what it's going people go insane. It's gonna get lost in the rabbit holes
Well, that's what happens and then the most constant rabbit hole is conspiracy conspiracy theories
Right, that's the most constant steady rabbit hole for me in long term and that literally
Literally has made me fucking go like I've had to
myself back so yeah
It becomes an addiction
conspiracy theories, okay the conspiracy there's
Are these conspiracy theories being presented to you or are these conclusions you make in your own mind?
No, I'm seeking information. For particularly conspiracy theories in this statement, it's me seeking information.
Uh, or varying, like, thoughts of how things, you know, can be, right?
You know, I'm just using that with, though, the conspiracy as an example, though, of me.
I delve too far down to rabbit hole each time, get addicted, and then, so, like, same thing,
why I didn't get into stones and crystals and fucking really far into rituals is because
I just delve so deep into the rabbit hole, I'll...
But but then it's gonna hit a point after maybe maybe at most a month where I'm like Raven. I know enough
I don't care anymore. I'm done
Like so many things I saw Raven's butthole Raven Raven Raven Raven Raven
little girl
Your kitty's packing
No, she's got a big, she's got a butthole on camera
No, that kitty starfish
Yeah, that kitty starfish is great
Better, you don't know any better
There are these, there are some
Coloring books is called I think they're called cats butthole. I think it's called cats
It's just like I've seen it. You see that one, too. Yeah
It's like best-selling. Yeah, what's up?
And it's like you can stick it on your cat's tail and like a little jewel that covers their little bottle
It's not that's good. If you're gonna come over to someone's house name a cat. It's their house
They want to show you their butthole. They're gonna do it
Yeah, hey, but low low you never
Low low and you don't ever see low. You don't low never shows her butthole. You never show your butthole, right?
Until psyche turns her around right now
You ladies you don't show it
I
Was watching you see yourself
Let's do you days holy shit. Oh
Oh, man
That was funny tonight. Oh page. You're in here for that
Hey, Lord Vader. Hey spunky. Yeah, Paulo
Was that in your stream?
When I was fishing the other morning, I guess I don't I yeah, you are yeah. Yeah
Cut like three fucking crawfish. Oh, yeah, the camera died. I didn't yeah
There was a little baby trout that took it and then it flopped off
Yeah, I have all these random verses like I look like I get beat up in my sleep
I don't know where they come from.
Hi, Spunky.
I got this one, and then I have one on my leg, and I have one on my leg, and on both
my legs on each side, that's like, I don't know, it's weird, they're like all kind of
the same.
Do you remember when I woke up with those burns page, remember those burns a few weeks
ago?
I'll show you.
They're almost healed for.
I need to do a cleansing in my home because I think that I'm just those look like claw marks
Yeah, those definitely look like like very well spaced out like claw marks
Yeah, who like unless you put yourself on the burner symmetrically like you know the symmetrical
I just woke up. I woke up with it. I woke up. It was just there when I woke up one morning
I have no idea how
You got some sort of demon chasing you
it's okay we can get rid of that's one of my specialties right so for once
okay I need to I need my guys I might need some help I need my
I need some spiritual help
yeah yeah yeah we're about doing exorcisms no guys actually no I do I've
been doing regular exorcisms like I've been doing really spiritual
You see it means you got a demon in the house. Yeah, I probably I probably did I don't know what happened
It was like, but it was like burns. It felt like burns. Yeah, that's why I have the sage now
You know because because you know because we have this negative energy and like, you know
Sometimes we act out of negative behaviors and it's like we can always like cleanse ourselves
Purify ourselves and you change your behavior, right?
So hopefully I'll have a demon in my house
Yeah, that would I could only imagine
I mean, I have cats. Is the cat. Oh no. I was going to say the cats. Oh, there's Remy.
Oh, I took a point. I had a cat. I had a cat named Remy because Remy is from a family
name.
Look at the butt tuffs, guys.
Terrible shedding.
Oh, God.
You just got, you got brushed this morning too.
He got brushed.
And last night.
Literally, I am in the cat shedding.
So the cat's white.
He's black.
Oh, God.
Yeah.
I have to bring a lip roller with me every single.
There's a lip roller in every area of my life.
Like at work.
I got this.
I got a stupid oversized one that's like a foot long.
I can't believe it's from Koska. We get like the multi-pack.
Koska?
It's the last one.
Where's the tickling one? It's got me nuts.
Yeah, I mean...
Oh, it's...
She's gonna win.
Did you...
finish pulling your cards?
You got a card for what? Your angels or what?
Don't yeah, oh, I don't yeah, I don't I well I have this food. I'll do the hoodoo chair
I'm gonna enjoy this whoo-hoo chair
I'll pull you one too, of course. Oh, you're gonna pull me one finally page, huh?
No shit
It's like the odd going tease of months page give me a reading
Well, you never go on my live finger reading either, you can come on there and get individual ones.
I don't like to take up Sykes channel with that, it's his stuff, it's his team.
Well, we have a page.
Well, well, if Sykes says it's okay.
Phillips, Phillips, come on, come on, panel, you know, maybe, you know, if you're nice to...
Me and my guests
We can be not nice to you know, I don't know if I have that in my body very much. Oh, you know what I don't
Yeah, right exactly how into your off-panel and I feel like I'm relevant again later on in the night
Okay, do you have a card? Thank you. Your your card is
That's Aunt Caroline. That's Aunt Caroline. Is this a tough tough tough broad
Yeah, it's Aunt Caroline
Okay, she's number 10
Let's see what it says. It says Aunt Caroline number 10
I'll have to look at the big index of this book. Okay. Aunt Caroline is page 152, okay?
So it says Aunt Caroline. This is the Wheel of Fortune card. It says
those Bible verse Ecclesiastes 3 1 says there is a time for everything and a season for every
activity under the heavens says the plant is hickory
The image, Aunt Caroline is standing in the doorway of her home in Newport, surrounded
by reporters.
Caroline died 1843-1918, aka Aunt Caroline, was born into slavery in South Carolina before
being relocated along with her parents to Arkansas.
After being freed in 1865, she married and began her work as a cartomancer.
Playing cards were her specialty. Aunt Caroline had been aware of her psychic gifts as a child,
and she quickly earned a reputation as an effective and reliable counselor.
Her clans were racially diverse, and it was not uncommon to see entire
trained cards of people disembarking in Newport to ask the Seeker's services.
Aunt Caroline was industrious too. She sold meals to crowds of people who awaited her.
She invested in land and property with money she earned. There was also a legend that she
buried a cache of gold somewhere in the area. After her death, many people tried to find the
treasure but were unsuccessful. Aunt Caroline's skill and amazing rags rich's story are two reasons
why she became a legend. It says when Aunt Caroline appears in her reading, it's an indication that
Whatever you're inquiring about rack your brain about
What you or someone else could have done differently if you like but the truth is that everything turned out exactly how it's supposed to
This could be a very hard pill to swallow in an age where people want to believe their thoughts or choices always dictate outcomes
The existence of a greater plan is not a welcome concept today because it implies vulnerability
Which is automatically translated to weakness in the minds of many
We are used to images of people casually walking away in slow motion from explosions or crashing through windows without a scratch.
We then want to be indestructible, unflappable people too. But this is not the movies.
We know in real life these characters most likely would have died in that raging inferno and that windowcrasher would have been blinded or cut to ribbons.
that those things didn't occur.
They liked the implication that the characters escaped
or were cooler than what fate had planned for them.
And Caroline teaches us that this way of thinking
is a fantasy.
No one can escape their fate
and incidents are no accidents.
She also teaches us to expect the unexpected.
The card may also be trying to tell you
To understand why things are happening or why they turned out the way they did, you
must consider the big picture.
If you receive anti-Caroline during a reading, consider the following.
Have you thought about turning that unexpected incident into an opportunity?
That was faded.
When one door closes, another one opens.
You was it really an accident your luck is about to change. You don't like change tough shit. It's about you
We're all players in one big chess game. Do you really think this is all about you get out of your own way?
Why were you born? Why are you here miracles happen every day?
You respect the cycle of life and how do you feel about getting older?
There you go. Thank you. That was a very great card and actually gave me lots of like, you know
It's him. I really like that deck. I really love that deck actually and yeah, I like their
Their way of how they made that deck of what it means to them and like they'll you know what I mean
That's what I love about different decks in general
It's all tarot based but it's the person that makes it the put the essence of themselves or their knowledge or what they see
Or how whatever the things that mean to them do in the position of those cards with the
Just all of it, right? So anyways, I really like that
There's good card. There's good card. Yeah for that
Yeah, you have a little ant Caroline spirit. Maybe like
What do you want like do you want
You just like one card from like the deck of your choice. I just want like one car like one. It's what one message like
Like that because I was kind of a long message, you know, but it was like it was like
It was good. It was good. Make it a good reading. Make it a good card.
You know what? It's like, let's do this for you. I'm going to do this one for you. We're going to do
one card for the enchanted map for you. Oh, nice. I like checking the map. Real quick,
the remnants of the weekend. I just want to show you what the...
Oh, you... Oh, there's everything in mud? My truck is...
oh that's all right okay that's muddy for a fucking for a GMC a nice new GMC truck
all right that's a muddy truck although I'm not I wish would I wish it would
been covered completely
There's only so much these little showstructs can fucking do.
Fucking Needle.
I'm not a GMC truck driver, right? That's not my personality.
Holy shit, it really is noticeably cooler in this fucking garage already. God, dude, some are fucking a genius.
Damn!
Time to wash it. Spongebob. Spongebob. You want to come up here ordering some just fun car readings and hanging out
Spongebob. Spongebob is really cool. I
See I
Say it's time for me to draw you tonight. I'm gonna draw you tonight. That's good. Well, okay. I'm gonna do my good side
No, it's just right here, right? This is my good part just my shoulders
You can leave my face out and the rest of my body. Just draw my shoulders. Okay. I got you
Here you go. Let's draw that. That's it. Let's draw straw that
All I did was turn I didn't it came aggressively flipping out but beautiful step right back on the deck
It's the talisman psych
Who's a talisman? Okay?
Okay, I don't know if the number 49 means anything to you mm-hmm
Almost the answer to the universe I
Haven't really read money in this book because I don't usually use it often for the books, but I
Guess we better do it
to use my books more lately just to like appreciate and I'm like
Um, you know recognize and understand like where where was the person that made the deck was coming from when they made it and why they made it
You know, I'd like appreciate that for them see what their interpretation is because it's not always what our first intuitive interpretation is if we are not using decks
I mean sorry on books about the writer also. Yes
Talisman so a lesson truly learned is crystallized as it as earned wisdom you have all you need for success for the success you see
So, wisdom allows you to recognize the traps on the road and familiar patterns that you
want to avoid.
It also enables you to quickly gather information about where you are on your journey.
It helps you recognize your abilities and know how to find the best routes along the
way.
Now you're at a place where you know the right thing to do is, and the best choice is to take
You really can't come, you can't really commit a mistake.
Whatever your inquiry, great fortune awaits you.
For you have the wisdom to arrive at the right decision,
you've learned your lessons
and earned the right to your success.
I love it Paige, thank you so much.
I mean, I didn't do a great job with the picture of Isaiah,
but you wanna see the picture of Isaiah?
Oh, it's big.
Sorry, I'm here, I'm here.
Hi.
Hey.
I say, is this good of you?
Yeah, yeah, good enough.
I feel like I look more Rasta than Viking, but yeah.
You look a little Rasta.
Right, right.
All right. Hey, everyone say hi to Sponky.
Are you on Sponky page?
Hi. You survived the camping night in the woods.
Oh, yeah. I'm like Sponky. I know you.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, I did. I did.
I survived that.
I didn't drown in that little fucking crick.
We're all good. You know, right here.
It was like watching the Blair Witch Project.
Fuckin then my cousin pulls me out at like at one point in time when everything's blacked out
He's like I've got to go walk in the woods. I'm like, dude, what what he's randomly woke up
Oh, I think I think it was on there when he tried to scare me
Yes, he was like running from in the woods trying to get you. Yeah
Shortly after that was he's like, you're always good walking the woods like dude. It's fucking like I really is dicks in the morning and pitch black
Why why?
Yeah, you were barely you weren't even around for that. No, I don't have it. I fall asleep
sometimes. Sometimes. Sometimes. Sometimes. No, it was a fun night. We had fun. It was
good. It was fun. Who else are we on with? We're paid. Have you got paid? This is paid.
Pages in Canada spunky. She's like awesome. Yeah, so we're always people like Canadians in the show
No, they're a little bit. They're a little bit different. We love this thing
Nice to meet you
and you just say that there's only like four or five of us that are from Canada let's be real
and they're all really cool though you guys love us and you all pronunciate the same way yeah we do
because we're canadian right yeah it's about to get I only say that when I'm really drunk or I'm
really talking fast okay so you're really drunk tonight or you're talking really fast
I lied I just say it I just say it I don't realize it till like you guys bring it up
She's about to read that deck.
Read that deck.
Can I read that deck?
Who wants...
Do you want one from this deck or would you like me to pull a different deck?
I don't know. I don't care.
I just don't care.
You don't know anything about the deck size or the deck.
It's about the motion of the shuffling.
I like a big deck.
I like a big deck, you know?
I don't think you said deck the first time.
Is it important to be wider or longer?
It's all about the shuffle. It's all about the shuffle. It's all about the shuffle.
It's all about the shuffle and it's all about the delivery and the message.
Yeah.
I wouldn't know because you don't part flash, but that's what I hear.
Well, I'm done.
I'm done.
Yeah, because some people say like, oh, like one card readings, like, you know how much
one card information, one card can impart you, you have much information.
Rather than like a lot of card, I think one card is better. Sometimes it can give you a message or a theme of what's going on for you
So I think I think one card readings are great too
I don't disagree at all
I just think whatever the
Yeah, whatever whatever deck she decides to shuffle based off of she's already got it in her hands or she wants to pick a different
somebody
That's a little competing. That was the reading I was supposed to have in the end no matter what
Hmm
Yep, that's usually how it comes out
Um, so I feel like
I mean, I do like to do a little bit of a challenging. I mean, I didn't do that for a sake, but
We did it yesterday. So it's fine. It's not like there was probably some super new news anyways
You know what I mean? I did do that yesterday. So
But I feel like you're going through a little bit of I
Think you're going through an emotional transition. I want to say emotional shift like emotional
Metamorphosis of some kind like there's things that you have
Have just had to like you look at things in a different perspective when it comes to matters of
heart and I feel like what you're seeking when it comes to like you know
you love yourself you found that like wholeness kind of within yourself like
you're you're comfortable with being in your own company now it's just like
enough to you know be
In a proper relationship and give somebody something without being like, oh, it's just gonna be a fling or I can't commit
I just don't want to be alone
I feel like you've gone through like just a bunch of transitioning and like maturing when it comes to what you want out of I
Think I'm really focusing spirits really telling me like a something about love or something not love
But like a partnership or competitive compatibility
You're thinking a lot about that too because I don't know if you had a rough
go with your last relationship but I feel like it really took you a long time to get out of them
out of the motions of kind of grieving that for a long time and understanding it
and I feel like you just woke up one day and not long ago and you were like you know what
fuck it I'm actually cool dude I'm actually not too hard to love and I didn't take I shouldn't
take all the responsibility for whatever all that happened right so I feel like you just you respect
yourself and you love yourself enough now that you feel like you might be ready to find and seek
compatible partner or somebody who's gonna bring some joy and some love and
balance into your life rather than it being like a toxic relationship I think
you've had mostly those and you're over them true that okay okay I'm gonna I'm
gonna pull cards now and stop talking see I don't need the cards but just for
you I'm gonna do it to clarify I'm not easy to read no buddy this is just what
you've seen me do it a million times I haven't that's the problem I haven't seen
you do the golden palace I told you I told you I told you I don't know if the
number 23 means anything to you
But you're your palace, you know what I mean you want you have created some sort of environment and within yourself as well that you feel
It's kind of like you feel it's enough of a palace to bring somebody into to enjoy with you or to share it with
Okay
She's so good in the house just that little blast
Hi Wellington. Oh my god. Oh my god
Holy shit
Oh my god
Yeah
The Golden Palace card represents good fortune, ambitions fulfilled, wealth, and prosperity.
It may also indicate, set the fuck up! Listen to this. Are you ready?
Okay, it may also indicate emotional fulfillment, as perhaps you're entering a time of happiness
that's long overdue.
The message here is that self-worth isn't measured by what you have, no matter how abundant
your life is.
Instead, it comes from what you are, how authentically you're living your life, and how much love
you're willing to share.
Granted, receiving this card does not indicate material gain and furthering of tangible rewards,
but things come and go.
And knowing your true value leads to even greater riches now share the wealth. What the fuck did I just say you guys?
Oh my god, I even freaked myself out with that one. Okay
Whew, that was weird. That was good. I mean, it's not weird, but that was like that one was felt good
That was awesome. Yeah. So Isaiah there's your reading. You waited a long long time for that. Was it worth it?
Don't answer that
he's not talking I think he's muted yeah we don't hear the words coming out of
your mouth yeah no I won't answer that then am I unmuted now yeah you're fine
to do something really quick though just to give you like a little bit of a time frame for like
one something because I feel like something's coming in for you and I feel like you know it's
coming to you but I'm going to pull you a mootology oracle deck it's a manifestation deck it's really
pretty look pretty pretty so anyway it kind of like will give you sort of like uh just a little
bit of I need to do it I'm just doing it okay I'm doing it sorry for all the jingling there's a
I don't want to sit like that.
Say hi.
Oh, look at this.
My kitties.
I used to have a Siamese cat named Yoshi.
This is Beans.
Hi, Beans.
Nice to meet you.
You're the baby.
And this is St.
Hello, St.
Hello, baby.
What are you doing?
I love you, big guy.
That's a cute name.
What a cute name.
He's not one now
You're still a crackhead. You are
Thanks, buddy, buddy
I don't know how you run around and it's fucking maybe so 90 degrees
meow meow meow
You little kitty cat
what's it banks you said banks banks and saints this is saint look at him sticking his head in the
Yeah, they're good little cats
No, my dogs are fighting
People are crazy. That's what that's about
Sorry, I can't get it out of my eyes.
There we go.
We're good.
You can do it.
Ooh, look at that.
I see we've got the new moon in Gemini so think it through. So whatever you're trying to make a decision about, don't put pressure on yourself about it, or don't put pressure on the situation and kind of getting a bit of a different twist here.
Just making sure that you're filling the right buckets for the right people and allowing don't
You sometimes you get a little over caught like you get cocky or like a little overconfident
Okay, because I feel like sometimes that really gets in the way of the of your flow of you and your life, right a little bit
Thinking things through and like taking a minute taking a breather just to like calm your just calm the sea inside for a second and then kind of
Decide and just use your discernment where and which and who did and what does that make sense that makes sense
It was extremely Canadian way to put that but it was also very paid. So we're gonna do one. Well, you didn't say a boot
So it wasn't that Canadians. I'm pretty
Didn't catch it
Oh, there we go. Okay. So, practice gratitude. So, being grateful for things, being grateful for all the things that you've learned.
Always.
Smile high.
Nice.
And so, we do have, like, we have sedatives, we've got Gemini, we've got cancer.
Shocking. Of course, there's Popsil.
Yeah.
Anyways, love you. There you go.
Thank you. Thank you. I appreciate it. I won't tell you if it was good or bad cuz you said don't tell me how that was
Thank you, though, thank you. Oh, you know, you know, you know, he loves you. Oh all day long. Absolutely
I love you psych. There you go. It's just a little
Spunky are you going to read tonight? I love that
Okay, well, I'll you want me to go first page or do you want it or is it okay page or
But what am I what are you doing? What are we doing? I was just reading
Spunky Spunky Spunky would like a reading like yeah
Do whatever you want
But will you do you'll do one I'm sure
No problem. Okay. I like when we do that back to back things like that. I don't think we do
Maybe check in the spice cabinet. Okay, this is a really interesting reading so far. Okay, so
If you look we got
We had the higher we have the higher fit. Okay, and they're higher fit
And that's Alice's sister, you know her older sister that's reading the book and Alice is like so bored because there's no pictures in the book or whatever
But she has this higher learning and it's like, you know
Either you seeking higher learnings be seeking an education about something the higher fit
Sometimes also connected to God, you know, also, this is like
Hierophant is always going to God but look but look at the other card I got with it. I got I got this world card
Look, so so look they're both. They're both sleeping. That's like
It's like you're very into your deep into your subconscious. There's something about you
That's that's like sleeping and it's like it's like in the kind of a fantasy or a dream
Like because it seems like let's see that
And I pulled both of these cars.
These are both of them sleeping.
That's crazy.
Yeah, but the world card is like,
this is like the end of a cycle,
like coming through a cycle successfully,
she's like just about to wake up right there.
The cat, I think the cat's about to like,
wake her up right there.
See, she's like starting to smile
and like wake up a little bit and so,
but yeah, and she maybe is not asleep.
She's just like deep and steady.
But it's like it's so it's like there's an awareness is there there is an awakeness because she's not sleeping
She's she's waking up and so there's like a I see like the spiritual awakening and then we have this like this emperor
I so I don't know. That's maybe this is the someone that's waking you up. There's like this kind of flashing guy
Okay page. There's a flashing guy there. I'll tell you about the emperor though the emperor and
The emperor's number four it says the king of hearts is a gentle
Leader who often tries to persuade his is a hot tempered wife the queen of hearts to be reasonable and keep her cool
The emperor represents a patriarch or authority figure who like the king of hearts
values good sense and self-discipline. Though it may be tempting to lose your temper, the emperor
reminds you of the importance of restraint. Now is the time to resist acting impulsively.
Instead, make sure you take time to respond thoughtfully to situations rather than reacting
That's good
That was good. I do want to say but the higher fit to the higher fit which is the first card it says
Though Alice's attention wanders her sister tries her best to keep Alice's focus on her history lesson
The higher fit like Alice's sister is a wise teacher who values education structure and tradition
Well, there may be a time and place for non-conformity rebellion the higher fit indicates. This is not it
Turn to experience teachers and authority figures for guidance now. Wouldn't you kindly pay attention? You have lessons to learn
And if you want to hear about the world card, which you got that world card too, because you got all these major cards,
it says, Alice's Adventures in Wonderland begin and end near the rabbit hole at the base of the tree on a beautiful day.
The world represents a satisfying completion of a long journey. You've come to the end of an important, life-changing expedition.
Whether this refers to actual travel or more personal internal journey,
you've been met with confounding challenges and joyous breakthroughs
and have learned many lessons along the way. You've reached your destination as a wiser,
more accomplished person. Enjoy your success. Oh, that's cool. Yeah.
What is Isaiah doing
He's got a dog over there
Everybody a TA exiled one everyone feel free to come up here. I did a little it was just like a two-second hang
It just just a lot
If I find my phone, I'll page page left. Oh shit. Oh
My god, I think I left my phone in my in my garage, but it's my fight. I think I did. Yeah
Didn't even say bye
But oh no, no home. No, because I had my phone when I was talking to the weed weed delivery guy, so I didn't do
You say weed delivery
Yeah, you motherfuckers in California eat a dick
I know I just I mean
I just I just got this I just got this is called the mile high has a little goat on it. Oh, you like to do it, right?
Totally in the goats. I have a goat tattoo
You know, it's it's bullshit because it's recreational here too. It's just free whatever
Not free, but you know, whatever
Walmart could sell it here if they fucking wanted to which is kind of surprising that happened started, but
Why can't we get it fucking delivered? What the fuck?
Well, it's record. It's recreational
fuck
Hopefully, I'll hear my phone sooner or later, but yeah, but I'm a some of Capricorn. I'm really into goats
You know that's not into goes not not a weird way, but no
There's such cool creatures
They are you know, they some can scream some can think so can climb trees some can
Yeah
Some can, yeah, and they can always get over any obstacle.
They eat anything, you know, they're really cute,
but they're very associated with,
sometimes associated with the devil,
the devil and, you know, some people say,
like, you know, there's a black sheep in the family,
I always say I'm the black goat of my family.
It's not that big, Psyche, it's not that big.
Oh, Justin wants to know a second if you got the McDonald's meal today.
I don't know what that means.
Yeah, I got a Big Mac for McDonald's and a couple of coffee.
Oh, it's all about the fish fillets, baby.
That McDonald's I live by the fish bar. I live on the pier. I'm not McDonald's fish filet is like not
You're right. You're right on the off the pier. It's very probably a similar price
No, no, no, I can get I get three fish chocolate for six dollars on happy hour
Very similar price then because McDonald's fish filets are two for six right now in our area
Okay, well, no, that's right three for six right so I get even more and it's like even better
If I wasn't lazy, I could go out to the lake that is right
you know like a five-minute drive and catch fish but yeah also that and also i'm
i'm i'm i'm i'm going to put the rest of that big mac i didn't need the whole thing i'm gonna
eat the rest of it i'm gonna put it in the oven for
maybe like 15 minutes 15 minutes I'll put on 350 bro just pull that top button
and I love the next flip the next so the middle bun to top on dude oh life
changing fuck the top on bro bless you thank you oh on top of the heat the
fucking pollen is outrageous here
It's bad everywhere. Yeah, I've been knocking myself out with Benadryl ever. I mean, normally I can't sleep anyway, but
Being in coughing and all the shit's even worse. So I I've been taking Benadryl for the last week every fucking day
I where are you at? Hey Benadryl up in Ohio
Yeah, just sucks
I hate Benadryl because I'm just groggy and fucked up because I can't do drowsy fucking allergy meds, but I
Gotta sleep so
Oh, I like that. Well, it's gotta be well, I need the drowsy dex. No, no, no, that's just it's not working like I have
Well, I have the Costco sir
Not doing shit for me obviously because that's what I took the night, you know
And that's the non drowsy shit, but Benadryl at least Benadryl just knocks me out. So I mean, I'm not teasing. I'm sleeping
Welcome back page
Sorry, Revington
Why are you the cutest puppy
Okay, so I missed that whole fucking meeting so what it was never mind. Oh, I'll watch it back
I actually would prefer that I didn't hear it because we're gonna see how these cards connect now to that. Yeah, that's good
We can do that. That's my favorite. I like look at all that
Look at all that ready
Um, what I'm going to do for you is I'm going to pull one of the cards from the animal spirit,
um, wild and known animal spirit deck, and I like this because this deck just, it's got a great,
great meaning in the books. Like, these don't mean the things that we would normally perceive them to
or have our entire lives or what that thing would represent. Also, um...
I like this is like my, my, I always call it my intuition, interactive reading.
So I'm going to not do a jump card for you, but I'm going to shuffle and I'll explain in a minute.
So just let me shuffle you guys. Can you do the thing for a sec?
Okay.
Interesting.
I don't know like they keep showing me water. Do you live near water? Are you going somewhere
where you're going to lake or going to the beach or frequently visit? I just went to the beach last
weekend. I live near water. Okay. Did you go with friends or family? My boyfriend. Okay. Oh never
Well, I'm glad that you guys had a good time. Did you guys get along the whole time?
Yeah, we did. Okay. Good. Good. I don't know why I was told to ask that. It's supposed to be funny
But only you'd get it. You know what I mean? Okay
Was it a water card?
Oh, God, I just got tea all over my face.
Are you okay?
Was it hot?
No, it's good.
It's actually this splash in my face because I had to drain my daughter's noodle things,
but she's...
Oh.
Mom, can you help me?
The eternal question.
Yeah.
Where is this? Where is this? Can I have that? Are we there yet? What are we doing? Can I have this over?
Yeah, it's a good time.
Okay, so this is what I'm going to do. We're going to do, I'm going to do shuffle. I'm going to,
you're going to tell me when to stop. You're going to say when.
Okay, stop.
Okay, now you're going to say that. Top, bottom, or middle?
Middle.
Okay, and this is an animal deck, but it also has like insects and like there's the odd like mythical creature in it
And like all water stuff, you know safari shit everything
So what do you think and don't think about it too hard if I you don't get an answer right away
Then you thought about it too hard first instinct. Which do you think it is?
What do you think it is you can even just say it's gonna be something with fur
Okay, I was just gonna fucking say you're gonna say something
Okay ready
Oh shit, you're wrong. I'm wrong. It's a dragonfly, but what we're gonna do we're gonna look at that
I'm nosy, so I'm gonna look at the top and the bottom and see also if that's a thing. Oh
No, not at all interesting. There wasn't even a single thing with fur even close
But that doesn't mean anything. So what does the dragonfly mean to you? I'm gonna ask you that. Oh
it kind of when I see them I think of like peacefulness and
harmony and just kind of calmness.
Okay, perfect. So now, um,
you're definitely going through this phase where it's like
You're finding that piece and that harmony. I'm finding some balance within maybe some sort of
Turmoil that you've had just recently. I'm not sure if it's gonna I'm gonna say family
But I also want to say that maybe it was with a friend as well. That might be like family
They're showing me just this dynamic like a family tree kind of being lit on fire or somebody with a match
It's like I'm gonna do it. I'm gonna do it. I'm gonna do it. You know what I mean?
Like infiltrating or being a
Martyr or meddler, you know, there's somebody with bad intentions or has been that you've been dealing with for a while
But I feel like you have recently had your fill and like cut them out somehow even though it was hard for you
And or maybe you have lost somebody that wasn't out of your it was out of control, but I do feel like mostly
I feel like the summing that you needed to cut off,
and it hurt a lot to do that,
but it did bring some peace.
And I feel like that's why I asked you that question
about you and your boyfriend.
I try not to get too personal, like up on here,
because I mean, deeper readings are different,
but I'm also unfiltered and I also can't lie, so.
Yeah, it has to do with my son.
There was like a massive blowout with my son,
and I actually sent him to his dad's house, so.
Okay, yeah, okay.
That makes sense. Okay. Cause there's definitely showing me family tree stuff or showing me like everybody's standing around it. There was, you know, anyways, let's, um, let's read. So that's beautiful.
I just have to say my only little thing sometimes before cards or, you know, because I don't want you to think I'm just reading a book. You know what I mean? It's not what I do.
I'm not really even a card reader, but I am, I guess, with a people reader, a soul reader, say that.
Okay.
So
Hmm. It was a winged thing, Harry.
Okay, Master of Light, Illusion, and the Mind.
The dragonfly is an ancient and ethereal creature that awakens a sense of wonder in all.
The dragonfly is a symbol of the mind as it is always moving, shifting, shimmering, and
changing.
When the dragonfly card appears, it's worth considering the quality of your mind and perception.
Are they restless or still, dreamlike or crystal clear?
The dragonfly reminds us to calm the mind so that the light of wisdom can shine through.
When in balance, it is clearly joyful, magical.
When out of balance, can't concentrate a busy mind.
To bring into balance, focus on the breath.
Focus on your breathing.
Um, I would also like to do just one of these.
Because this is your first reading here, so you've got to make it magical and memorable.
Okay, I'm gonna do one of well, I guess whatever comes out. So these are the four spirit messages
It's a really nice deck too. It kind of just is other things you need to hear. I suppose
So we'll just do a quick card for that and then we'll move along
It will be resolved soon like it will it'll it'll simmer down soon
I think you're feeling, you know, you guys have had a little time apart, right, for a
minute.
So it's just taking a breath and it's kind of gathering, recalibrating, you know, so
you don't say mean things and you know what I mean?
Kind of just taking a minute.
Absolutely.
It'll be fine though.
And I know that you're not, you know, sleeping at night because of it and I know that you're
sad in the day sometimes because of it, but just don't, don't let it fuck with you too
much, Mama.
You're all right.
You're okay.
You're empathic. Hey, you know that. Yes.
Right. Definitely. I knew. I knew.
You're also a healer, but you're a different kind of healer.
You help heal the mind in a sense.
It's like a lullaby and I don't know.
It's something about the frequency of you or your
Your voice or something like that. It's crazy. I actually work in medicine, but I feel like so much like a therapist
Perfect, okay. Thank you. So seek you got seek
The power of spirit exists in all things everything is okay. That's so funny
Okay, that you're gonna shit everything is made up of energy and every single thing in your physical world contains a fragment of spirit
Including you we are all one with spirit and always will be connected to one another
So it's just funny how I said something about like that the frequency of you of you being a healer like it works
Just in such a unique way your gift and that we all have gifts
It's just a matter of like recognizing and nourishing and
And all of that stuff right like they come later in life for some people like mine. I've had since I was like
I've always been this way
So soul solitude so that's you just kind of taking a little bit of time and reflecting and kind of
Reassessing a situation or a few scenarios right and just kind of like analyzing them so that you can use your gift to
Fix it. You're just you're a fixer. You know what I mean? You're like, I got to fix it
You like to fix things. So do I. Definitely. So soul solitude when your soul needs attention
There are moments when it's important to get away not oh, this is why I asked about the lake too, right?
It's like this all just correlates. It's lovely. So not just from the a noise outside of the outside world
But to find a place where your soul can experience peace and quiet a place for soul solitude
This is a time to pause a time to reflect in a time for you
So you're just, just keep doing what you're doing.
I feel like you already know that though.
So there's nothing that me or Psych can say
that it's not just giving you clarity
for what you've already feel, know and see, right?
But it is nice to hear it from someone else that is like you're not crazy
You know exactly what you're talking about and what you're doing and that you can listen to yourself
And I feel like that soul solitude gives you that clarity like when you do that
It's like you can trust your own advice
You can trust yourself and what you do and believe in that you know
But everything will be okay, and I'm glad that you went and you got away this weekend and went to the lake because that's very very healing as well
Thank you very much. Thank you for letting me do that and tap into your energy. How invasive
You said about
I feel filled for the night just Justin just said that was crazy spot on
Where's Justin? Why ain't he on the chat?
He's watching wrestling
What kind of wrestling does he watch? WWE or like or like, you know, that's exactly
WWE
He's a big kid. Yeah. Oh my god. Yes. He's a giant kid
I still watch wrestling too, so it's no big deal
As I say, I say we're the making good wrestling character. We were sitting here and there was somebody on the screen that looked just like him
I say I say the resident flexor you know flex
Okay, that's fine. You only get shoulders because it's really fucking hot out here. It is very hot outside
Oh, I don't really want to flex anything else. Oh, there we go. There you go. Ladies, that was a treat. That was a treat for the ladies, for all the ladies.
You can say it's good.
Any gay man, whatever.
He's flattered. He's flattered. He ran out with the guy once. He opened his mind.
He has a fucking girl, no doubt.
No, he, no, no, I said he made out.
I said, I say, I say, I say I made out with a guy once.
I say, I see.
Maybe I remember this conversation one way back
when we first met, Isaiah.
Were you guys talking to both of us?
Oh, he talks about it, a boot it every time.
Well, you shouldn't have told him a boot it, ever.
All right, no shit.
I learned after a few times on chat
that he's a boot telling everybody about it.
Well
You said it you said it publicly on my show wasn't like it wasn't like
You told me in confidence you told the whole show
Hey, if you bet I say he made out with a dude, I don't know I don't care. It's like
Oh
What's that? Weren't they dressed like a woman though or something?
So that's probably why it was attracted or at least attractive enough because it was a smaller dude
It was not a tall big dude. It was a small skinny dude. Okay. Okay. I like small and skinny so that's
Makes sense to you know why that would happen because I can't imagine making out of with a burly male
Burly bearded man. Oh, was it was he a twink? Was he a twink or no? Yes. Oh, yeah twink all day for sure
So a twink a twink you found his bear that night. That's so sweet
But then you said if you are a few hours a few it was a few it was a few hours later a few days later
You decided that wasn't for you. Oh
So that was more than 10 years. Jesus Christ. I don't fucking remember.
It was many moons ago.
Uh, it was... yeah, no, it was... I would say no more than 48 hours.
Well, we're just...
Because I don't want to be a liar.
I wish I never did that shit ever.
No
CB was made out with a girl. I kind of liked it and so guys, you know, everyone
Experimentsy, you know, I that would mean I would have
Hi CB, we're all born by like real quite humans are naturally by serious
Exactly. And you find out what you're into and I found out I'm not into dudes at all.
The older I get, the more I find out what people are about and it's fucking crazy.
Yeah.
Yeah. There's some shit out there.
It's hurtful.
It's fucking insanity out there.
Truth.
Are you single-page or do you have a partner?
I'm going through a split of nine years, it's been going on for a month now, so I'm newly single.
I'm sorry, that's hard. I was going to say if you're out dating, it is crazy.
She broke up with the Jeeps.
That's good. You like that. I know
You know that right like
Have you been out on any dates page
Okay, the internet is so scary they're dating apps are so scary they're
He's out there. He's he's out there doing it. That's so I would like well
Maybe I'll try to see what so I went on tinder and I feel like I was shopping for human beings
And I fucking hated it and it was a tender socks. I tried that too, right? Right cuz I got out of 13 years recently
I didn't like it. No, so I'm trying to come on the panel right out Chris does road cheese
I won't you to come on the panel, but I know Chris
Yeah, he doesn't have his camera or his or microphone. Oh, Justin and I met on hinge. Oh, you did. Oh, yeah
Another dating
Yeah, yeah, no, I don't much prefer the internet. I'd rather
Oh, I think he froze I say it froze
Yeah, that's just a picture. Don't you love when one of us freezes or doesn't realize our mics off
And we'll just go and chat and then we turn it on. It just doesn't even face a beat. We're still just talking
Hi T. Why what's up, buddy?
Hey pay it tastes like dress on like shit. I'm a little bit back up right now. Like it's not he knows
I sound like a ghost. It's not what you said
I don't know what happened. I'm feeling a little sick today
I
Thought if I was with you go so I rub paper over your shit
So I got you you know what I would want to come up here and say that cuz I knew you're gonna say that
No, I thought you were gonna say is it oh go see sick? I if you were with me
I'd take care of you. That's what I thought you're gonna say I take I take your trip rich directly
Now with the thermometer though
Yeah, you crossed you crossed it. There you did. Well, it wasn't even a minute you crossed one brother
like 30 seconds in 30 seconds 30 seconds in you did on purpose solidity I'm bad bad I'm bad
and when you said that all I seen was a beard from homeboy up up top
I feel like my voice sounds like shit too I think I see have you watched uh 28 years later yet
Um like a long time ago is not why no the 28 years the new one that's in the movie theater right now
You look like the alpha
Hey, I'm calling you alpha. So you should take the compliment in that
Now talking to you brother
The alphas I'll be I mean the alphas I'll be I guess
Like you, you'd be like, I wouldn't want you to eat me if you were a zombie.
You what? You'd be a, you'd be a hunger. Wait, what?
You said you want me to eat you. No, you wouldn't, wouldn't you just say
you're going to fucking listen to me and I'll tell you. Okay.
Well, you're not. You're just going off. Okay. So I said, like, if you were a
zombie, I'd be sick. I'll do it. You're a hungry guy.
Like you would probably be eating brains all day long.
You'd, I would never, and I don't think like going for their brain.
Well, then I'm safe that I'm safe
Yeah, Chris. Are you here? Hey, did you know what I think we'd agree with that?
Right, right there was a different statement earlier
I think I heard exactly what he said nothing. She's changing it up
Bosses on you
Damn right who wants a beer ride you guys can eat each other have fun. Oh god
No, no, no remember I tried that once and I didn't like it
Well, I mean to argument's sake I would if I was a zombie I wouldn't eat any of one of you because don't zombies go for brains
Yeah, and you don't have to wait wait, but I caught that
Therefore, I have a brain. Thank you. You know, I work all day on that joke and
That's a good one with the key appeal zombies where the the racist the racists were racist
The zombies are walking across the street away from key appeal
Oh my god, oh that that was a good segment. This is elian see but yeah, the zombies do like
Yep, I like the elian one
Oh, you're the alien the alien was the same fucking thing pretty well. Yeah, that was
All the white guy wants to be with us. No, he's
I can't believe that I don't know if it's pillar it's one of them I forget he's one that make get out
Is that peel
I don't know if it's the shorter one, but yeah, he makes some good movies, dude
Yeah, you make some good actual good movies
That was Jordan feel because he's the skinny one. I believe skinny bald one
Yeah, yeah
Sound reboot that he did
No, no did no is it good
Some of them are good some of them are really weird
Well, that's the Twilight Zone. So that's yeah
Yeah, I like that pretty good then because the Twilight Zone is just weird
Yeah, I mean, I love that kind of
So the old Twilight Zone was like a grown-up goosebumps
I can't.
By the way, I've watched a couple of the Goosebumps back in the 90s, and that shit is still freaky,
so a couple of those actually, like I don't feel bad for being scared for those, like.
Listen.
The plant one in the basement.
I dare.
Just one sec.
Let me just say it.
Then you can listen to me.
Okay, so listen.
The fucking new Goosebumps.
Have you seen them?
No.
I was like, really, I was like, just a minute ago, I had my leg, my leg, or whatever.
So couldn't, I had to watch TV and that came on randomly, like new goosebumps with like Ross from fucking friends was in it.
And it was actually pretty, I could not, I could not stop watching the stupid fucking show. I watched it to the end.
I can't imagine not just watching awkwardly, because that's just Ross being awkward.
Ross would freak me out too.
He would be the awkward, yeah.
Also though, because I know-
But it's just like a dad in it, it's weird.
That's why you're gonna say you had your leg over your bed and you like freak the fuck out because
I was gonna grab your legs. We all have that fear
She turned the controller for
The scary scenes and you know leg over. No, all right. All right. All right. All right the goose bumps where it's like the the fucking dock
Obviously, I cannot remember the title of that
But every like the uh, the the dead fucking drowned people are trying to drag them
off the dock into the water with them?
Yeah.
That was one of the worst because I didn't go in the water for like a fucking year after that as a kid.
One I still don't go in the water. I
Got a talisman brother off. I wouldn't go to I wouldn't even go to a pool unless I see the bottom of that bitch
Fuck that if you can't see the bottom of it
I got
Paige, I think you got what is it called talent talent talisman phobia talisman phobia
I don't know
You have to live until you swam in the middle of the Great Lakes man
I don't like fish in the middle of the great lakes and it's fucking creepy
They've been fishing out there when you can't see sure fuck that
It was like just pull a fault a two-foot fish out of the water, and then you jump in and go swimming
No, no, it's the ponds. It's the standing water against me, right?
Like if it's a small pond and like, you know small like no, I'm not about that life because I just think if we get a
cats
You know what if I get a cat it's gonna be Dave Fred Durst. That's just
Fred Durst looks so old lately man
He just played in a movie he just played in a movie with
It was called like a why 2k or whatever he he was in that movie and he looked old as fuck, but he still had his hat on
There's a fucking they were fighting like robots and it's called white UK
I had a couple of good actors in it. Believe it or not. It's a movie, but
I saw them in concert, I saw them in concert before too.
I would love to have, that would have been awesome, I do like Limpiscan.
Old Limpiscan, I don't, I don't know if they still make songs because I don't, yeah, fuck that.
You know they sound like some fucking band.
He went country.
He did?
They just made three songs and I still...
His look he did.
Oh, cowboy hat with the button up, you know, but
Post Malone my country
Are you gonna sing us one page guitar fucking awesome though and he can sing country pretty fucking
can you sing can you sing a country song can I sing us a little country song page yeah page do it
but her sing first and then we'll all have one and we'll all join in
i'm not gonna sing because now i'm on the spot so now i don't i want to just go under the table
kind of i respect you for not singing singing underneath the table then girl yeah hey do you
have a guitar i don't have a guitar but i'm playing guitar a little bit
I got a cowboy. Hey, you know, I think Mr. Pick a few strings. Hey. Oh, okay. She's going to go that time.
She puts it on. She's singing. If she puts it on, she's singing. Yeah. Fuck. Yeah. I think we all agree with that.
She's coming back in a full. She's gonna come back in a full. I'm waiting for hers. I got mine ready.
I'm not singing up. My voice is terrible. She's gonna come back in a full country, country, uh, cowgirl.
I want to see her in the Daisy Dukes. Yeah.
It's going to be glittery.
Oh, yeah.
There you go.
Sing us one.
Hey, come on.
Yeah. Come on. Alright, here you go. If she's not stinging, I'm gonna crash out. I get to put mine on now. It looks like you're finna crash. Yeah, go ahead.
You're already crashing out. Okay. Now we got, oh, we got a duet coming up. Oh, I like it. Absolutely not.
Tech, you see I'm already crashing out.
Sat down and cried.
Sike.
I sit down and cry. That's it. What the fuck are you doing?
I'm a cowboy Indian. I'm a literal Indian and I'm also still a cowgirl. I don't know.
It's a cowboy Indian. Sethers, hats.
Can we get an Indian song?
If the Cowboys and Indians fell in love and had a child, it would be cool.
Yo, what the hell?
Your Indian name would be, uh, Reeds a lot or, uh...
No, my...
I'm trying to be respectful.
I don't like that one I don't know if this is offensive or not
But I was mentioning Indians to someone and they went dot or feather, and I about died cuz like
It's true
Yeah, I was like, oh
Why'd you put your head away?
in the house is kind of not a thing you do in the house well that depends he asks a lot of you
I know you fucking put your stereotype on that. That is who do you think got your cowboy hats up there in kanukia, huh?
I'm offended you
I'm just saying that I was very
The westerners, southern westerners
And you never lay your hat flat down you lay it up, it's bad luck
No, that's not flat down. Mine's low
I say I say that hat is been through some things
I don't have a sticky head up here, I'm sorry, I can show you I don't have a sticky head up here, I can show you I don't have a sticky head up here, I can show you I don't have a sticky head up here, I can show you I don't have a sticky head up here, I can show you I don't have a sticky head up here, I can show you I don't have a sticky head up here, I can show you I don't have a sticky head up here, I can show you I don't have a sticky head up here, I can show you I don't have a sticky head up here, I can show you I don't have a sticky head up here, I can show you I don't have a sticky head up here, I can show you I don't have a sticky head up here, I can show you I don't have a sticky head up here, I can show you I don't have a sticky head up here, I can show you I don't have a sticky head up here
You've all been sat on, did you sit on all your hats?
You've sat on all your hats accidentally.
This is not a sit on, well okay,
this one probably did actually.
What are you on my shirt?
I got 30 hats and zero T-shirts.
They're all in shape, why are they all misshapen?
Fuck, I've moved him all the way.
I was like, why don't I have any fucking shirts?
I found a pile of them sitting to my left
right here on this fucking basket
because of being on fucking chat every night,
or, you know, at night,
and I never would take my fucking shirts
and a fucking wash-up or shit.
All of my t-shirts are fucking out here.
Yeah.
I thought you were gonna say this
because you bust through them when you flex.
Yeah.
Uh, no, thank you. Thank you. Yes. Thank you. You're right. That's why. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know.
No, that's cute. Did you just steal that from Isaiah? Yeah
All right, this is all right now run with me here undertaker hat
Yes
Whoa dark holiday. Ooh, I like it. Ooh, I like that
Door the Explorer obviously
Let's see what
Give me a second, I'm gonna find a shirt to put on
My helmet you guys keep fucking around what a fucking hat
Had so my gosh
Go see like that
Go see by curious
No, yeah, there you go
That looks like a T. That looks like a second great teacher
Or that or that old white money in the south and I don't like black people. Yeah
Page it's a fucking great hat
She's going back for more by the way
I can't even I don't even know where my rest of my hats are. I got a whole lot of stupid fucking hats
I came to win. The hard hat is the only hat. Oh and the fucking V for Vendetta. Ah, oh god damn. Let's go
Isn't that the criminal for Dominic Sonic and the Hedgehog the the girly steampunk fucking
Whoa, yep, yep
Now we can't see shit. You walked in the dark
That's a great fucking hat come on
I just have a crown hold on
It better not be working
I can pull the best hat ever that everybody will get offended about
Mmm, I can't what do you get other what is it your KKK hood like?
Don't tempt me. Don't tempt me. All right
There's the quick flash I gave the quick flash I used to I I would forget I was wearing that hat I
Ended up like in this fucking like God. We're
It was
Where was oh no was in Virginia and I was wearing that hat all through this fucking portion of Virginia and Virginia's very very liberal
I didn't even realize the hat and I'm like everybody's staring at me some stupid fucking kind of way
Yeah, I know what the do-doh is that my buddy that I was staying with he's like you didn't realize what you fucking walked out
We're in I'm like no I put it like you like I'm dressed like
Your hat I'm like what hat he's like
Like oh
Oh my god. Oh my god.
Chris. Hey, what's up, Chris? How are you? Who's embarrassed? I'm good. You know, Paige?
You're Paige? Yeah. Silly. That's oldy, Chris. Come on. All right, so I'm going to win. Yes.
Yeah. Fuck yeah. There we go. Oh my god, Paige. Oh my god, Paige.
I
Go to the ice white shit with you party every day
Well page with a head like that I can understand
Hi, I never once said I've never once anything about that forehead
I was thinking five head but
But it was inside of it when I grabbed it so I'm like I'm putting it on
Can't put people on full screen
Let's see I found I found some of my hats though. So let's see if the other stupid ones are in there. What's my dog?
I don't know
Easy yes, Monica come on up
Monica come on up in my link and I think my link is pinned
These are some of them. Oh shit. Oh my gosh, what is he doing? Here's a smashed one, but I don't know why I bought this
I kind of felt like I don't know weird fucking almost school shoot. I don't know that weird that weird artsy guy
You know what I'm talking about, right?
Look, there's me.
Monica?
Yes.
That's me in the middle.
Here you go.
Here's my weird, the weird Archie guy that is
probably into anime hat.
I just, I just wanted to say thank you to Paige, what she did for me last night that she was so home and I really appreciate it.
Awwww.
That's it.
He was asleep and I couldn't come up.
This head is too small for me.
Awwww.
Thank you so much.
I just wanted to tell you that when you picked the purple, that's like my favorite color.
So you were like, it was really weird.
I am really weird, but honestly, if I wasn't, I could be in a purple with a little straight jacket in the nut house with kiddie slippers right now.
I'm not there yet, but the people keep clarifying that I'm correct.
It throws my buckets to know that it filled yours.
You know what I mean? That's my payment for it in a way.
Would you like to compliment me too?
You know I'm crazy.
I'm a Leo you heard
you. I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. I
know. I don't know. I don't know. I
I don't know what that is. I
don't know what that is. I have
Yeah, well, then yeah, never mind
Wait, thank you, January, right
January
I didn't have good birthday
Yeah, yeah, I'm January I'm January I'm early January. Oh, so yeah, you're not
I'm I'm I'm the lion. You're
here. Alpha. Your birthday's
coming up. Are you going to
wish me a happy birthday?
Happy birthday. It comes up.
What? No one comes up. Are you
July? Oh, you're scratching
Mabel. No, okay. Mabel, don't
do that shit again, Mabel.
Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go.
I'm December so it's right on the day of
Yep, passman
Okay, okay, I'm sorry to date you can you give what what year were you born?
Oh, okay. All right. All right.
That works. That works.
1970? That's cool.
That's all right. No, it's it's it's
What is going on or does that hat? What do you mean? Oh, no, that's a bad date. Well, now it's not a bad date anymore
Thank you. Appreciate that. Now. Are you a numerologist?
No
Now page was Isaiah up here last night that one it done the other readings that um, okay. Oh, okay. Sorry
The one who panics that was Chris
Oh
I don't know
Because he's not here
No, I just asked
Okay
He doesn't come up very often either when he does like I don't know. He was out of his element last night
He was just stealing off I think
But I stepped up and encouraged and helped
Took over I didn't mean to but was he crashing out?
No, he has a different style of reading where he like he like isn't getting specific details
And if the person doesn't agree with the detail that he gets kind of mad he's like he's like you're lying
He's like you're lying. Is that you're supposed to look at a badger your terracola
He would love me then you're reading did it would love me great aunt that she
By name and middle name
With her birthday. Holy shit, you know psyche. I knew you were a fraud. You can't even tell me what my great-great-grandma's name is
Yeah, I mean, I'm not gonna be a profit. Let's let's not get confused
What I think it would be a Mabel also picked one shit
Because it was either slave family or German or Irish so those are not very
No, no, no, no, I think yeah, no, I think yes, I think Chris I think Chris has a lot of talent in it
It's like oh, but it's again. There's an approach to reading there's an approach to reading
I would like say I would say maybe just your approach like
like, you know, I was
I would address Chris like this like I can't predict the future, but you're reading I think that your great
Grandmother's name was dumb dumb and then we went from there and I would okay
All right Chris here, do you do tarot also? I don't do
Oh, sorry, I thought you're part of me so sorry
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm
sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Okay, I wonder if she's fighting us to get them teased.
They're cute.
They're so cute.
Bitey ass.
You're right eight thousand dollars. Well, it's my one hell of a dog one hell of a lawnmower
It's a Remington. He's an idiot. Oh look how big and pretty
80 pounds of well, he's half shepherd half black lab. So 80 pounds
He's 70 closing in on 80. I know he looks small. Hey, that's it. Fuck
Osmo's 120
He's only eight months old
He's got plenty of growing left. Oh, yeah. Yeah, they said the 12th of what 14 months
No, I have a Malamute Wolf as well. When you close in on around it's almost three years old there
That's when they're like the rolling style
Yeah, 24 is usually like that's when you get the real idea of what size it's gonna be and then
My wolf dog even at two and a half he hadn't filled out fully yet. Yeah. Yeah, they like dogs are usually three by three
They're usually like that. They're done growing by three
the
I
Just saying this point not out
Worked, you know, I have to say something you're a German Shepherd has a little bit of looks like
Yeah
I mean, I've seen the German Shepherd build but I kind of see more coloring of the
Rot just in his face as soon as you pull like
When you look at his underside, it's just a straight German shepherd neck and coloring
all the way down.
He walks like a shepherd.
No, he's half German shepherd and half black lap.
So he's fucking retarded and he's going to be pretty big.
He won't be retarded for long.
I hope not.
I mean, he started pretty smart and then he's been retarded for the past couple of months.
So, you know, I hope he's got it back.
I got a I got a huskie miss with the primary and it's like a two foot little
like a two foot little look in a
house key or a lot of even make them like that
that's how I've always been expensive as well you
you know that's what I have homes key money for
I baby sat one or a dog sat one one time and I have a full size wolf dog as well and I got a picture of them two on the couch together.
It's hilarious.
Oh my God.
I mean, is she beautiful?
Is she cute?
Yes, but she's not.
She's not a guard dog like she tries to be, but she's like, she's literally like you just like punch her away.
Like she's so little.
Not a guard dog, an alarm dog.
Yeah, that's yeah, but she doesn't she doesn't howl like a husky
She doesn't thank you spunky. Good night, sweetheart. Thank you so much for being here
Thank you for the show
She's the dog that alerts and then gets like literally field gold plundered
Yeah, I mean if you're at least she's on your armpit like hey protecting doing
I live in the bush and my pup, she's a cally Pyrenees.
She'll hear something, go storming out the door
and then stand at the end of the driveway
or like at the top of the hill of the driveway
and bark until the boys get behind her
and then she's off to the bottom of the driveway.
Yeah, exactly.
Or at least she knows the boys are there, let's run it.
she's fucked she's fearless once she knows the boys are behind her not you go that's just like a wolf's man
Chris are you Canadian? Yeah. All right. There we go. Okay. The best dog. I unless you're alone wolf
Wolfs don't pack one-on-one. They have to have the pack behind them and the alpha is the one that
I don't know let's do it. But there's a stigmas. Don't forget stigmas. Not just alpha and beta though.
There's stigmas, there's stigmas, stigmas.
My wolf dog knows that I'm alpha, but he's not beta necessarily.
Oh, is he a boy? Oh, how much fighting did you do for that?
Oh my god. He knows you run that pack though. Let's make an argument.
He knows you run that pack. I've had my shoulder ripped open by my own dog on driving down the highway.
Yeah, I can only imagine it's a it's the constant fight. Oh man
You can you can get a girl wolf dog and it's I mean obviously way easier but a male you're constantly fighting
Well, you're you're fighting for dominance a lot. You're fighting a dog
Like do you any of you do like you Americans know what a badger is?
Why would you want to constantly fight a dog killed a badger by himself?
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
will say it will come up if you share it, yes, maybe
Well, no, don't just put don't just post it now actually that's like you this is not my channel ask him
I don't know
Your screen probably not good idea
Okay, so like we don't talk about where we're from or anything because that's doxing but anyway
So just so you guys know I actually know I met Chris at my work that golf course that I started at or whatever
They work now shit
So like I know him in real life
So I brought him here and then there's also someone else down in the chat that I've noticed
It sounds like 15 that's hanging out too
that I know in real life.
Does she have a wolf?
All right, Chris.
Oh, my god, the Canadians are taking a look like this.
Did she look as good in person, Chris?
Say again?
I said, did she look as good as person?
One?
Yes.
Hey, guys, hey, guys, hey, there's Spunky.
Hey, there's Spunky just got the membership.
Hey, there's Spunky, who was just on the show.
He's got the gifted membership.
Oh.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
that cool pictures I don't fucking
Hey guys, if anyone wants it guys if you don't want some do membership tonight. I'll match. I'll match if you don't any membership
I'll match you so
That's a deal. Oh, yeah, I did get my membership on dono. Let me see my PayPal work now. Hi if you don't know me
Argentine doggos. They are interesting breed. Oh doggos. Argentine doggos. Oh
Yes, she's awesome, I've known her for like nine years eight or nine years
Awesome
Is it is it Trudeau
that
You guys see them. Hey, oh look at this dog. Look at this dog. Hold on.
Wow. Look at a wolf. It's a wolf dog. Hi, guys. Hi, guys.
That's what scares me that he'll
kill a badger but he's gentle
enough I can let a three year
old walk him on a leash. Oh
that's good. Or take a bone out
of his mouth. Well that's good.
Would you guys like to see the
biggest dog die now? Yeah. Yeah.
Well what then I have to show
myself so I'm not going to do it.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
The best dog I ever had was a
border collie. Oh, dude. Oh, I
believe that. That's what my
puppy is. Border Collie, Pauli,
or uh Pyrenees. Are they not
the smartest dogs out there or
am I in? I don't know but I
never talk. I never talk
Barkley anything. You would
just tell me. Summer. Thank
you. Summer. Summer. Thank you
I'm trying. I'm trying. I'm
trying. I'm trying. I'm trying.
I'm trying. I'm trying. I'm trying.
I'm Barclay was about 65 pounds
65 to 70
The shit
They're fucking massive
I'm pretty sure Myron has a
smarter dog. My dog has
my black hat. I love a
the thing about them, they're
and you cannot. They're not
they will roam. Thank you
She has not been on a leash
after I got her. Wow. Usually
is the roamers. Yeah. The same
Oh, no, that dog's never on a leash ever ever ever
Well, baby, that's why you got that
It's called a W it's called a W that's what it's called
A win is a win regardless
Look my dog picked out a shiesty for me to put on as my next hat. He picked it. Not me
Maybe it's terrible terrible
I'll look that up
I know she's gonna be nice and hang out, but she must be mad at me. She wants to and that's that's coming from ghost the
Debater are you just be nice and hang out everyone. I got a boat to pick with beta. It's not that all right all night long
Wouldn't even pick a bone with her if you want to join you'd be nice. We'd all just hang out like we're doing now
That's you leave me in the back room the whole fucking time throw me on
But I want to feel welcome I want to make sure like we're cool
Yeah, we'll also for you
But no
You know pager you know what you should change your name to you that should be page
Timstone
Why you've ever watched that Western movie?
Happened hi Chris
Say that that
It's it's giving
My first time talking to you
Thank you so much. Thank you so much. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
that beautiful wig
What my hair?
No, it's okay. No, I was talking about not you mark. Obviously
Monica had a they were doing a hat off and she put a hat on which it was a really cool hat and then she had a wig on too
The pink wig was awesome
It was how did I blink out for the fucking thing? Oh
You know I didn't have a choice in that because my shit became gray and I didn't really have a choice
I don't know. Oh, see, you, you
don't really get to try it on.
The problem is the melon in your
skin and your heritage because
black don't crack. So, I don't
got great Asian. Don't raise
it. Is that the correct term?
What about a reason? I'm more of
a Latina man myself, but great
book. Raising to the sun.
That's why I got to fight the
president. Hey, don't I love
Who said that who said hydrate it great one of you just said I heard it
Age of all people. Oh my god, let them ship it boys
You said great now. We got it in the stream. Oh fuck. Do you say hi?
Look what you did page
What is it? What is it? What is
it? What is it? What is it?
What is it? What is it? What is it?
No, I was I was up at 430 this morning and go go go go going doctor women didn't pull that
That's radical you might win. I didn't ask earlier. I know
Oh, it's like he's still there. He's fucking around the back behind the curtain. He likes to do that fucking creeping on his couch
What you got on your neck you look like honey lead fuck yeah, what's your neck boy you heard yeah, and I mean, you know
I'm sorry, but that you know
It's pretty accurate
Tommy the the drubber okay, okay, yeah
Yeah, he looked like
Right and in gimp get up, you know like uh the the the submissive one
That's comedy
A gimp mask. Oh shit. No, no, no, uh, although if he's got a gimp mask the collars
That'd be pretty funny
Wow
I
They say motherfuckers don't know that don't show face there goes that's the one time y'all go get it again
They they also say the motherfuckers like this is not I've been cool all night
They also say motherfuckers like to debate and I'm pretty sure I've talked to you
But I've also talked to your boys and check the score next time
Before you talk to me check the score. See you see how much
Talking to me, it's all right. We don't hang out
All you know is you know nothing you don't know what the fuck you're talking about if you'd like to run it we can run it
Okay, we don't want to run them out then be quiet
I don't know what you're talking
about. Maybe you should fucking
say hi. Hi. Yeah, exactly. Hey,
don't make me go next door.
Go where the fuck do you want?
Check the score. Wherever you go.
Let me find out. It's an
invisible scoreboard. Let me find
out because the points don't
matter. Points do matter when
you're debating. You actually
don't know what the fuck you're
Like I didn't want to take it there. I want to say how many screenshots come out
How many people come on the panel with my face on a screenshot, you know
Well, and I'll end it by this I'll end it cuz I'll be the bigger man
screenshot whatever you want
This board you whatever you want you whatever you want go ahead
Oh, fuck. What is that?
I closed shut up. Oh, you know, you did it. It's probably me. So yeah, no you did it fuck off
Whenever you want
Everybody from my side, you already know what it is
Support psyche right now
Psyche right now come to psyches awakening terror everybody on what time it is come here to like subscribe no notifications. Thank you
I don't know how to share this
I put the link on on your page easy when we were over there
That's a cuteness but tonight
Yes on my face
my fucking best I'll go full I'll go full ninja mode I was like you know what
fuck that wait I've been live before I've been I'll show faith before I just
didn't want to have a pimple on my face right now because I just saved the other
day and I caught a pimple so I was like a little man was was that your face the
Tommy Lee I said yeah yeah no no no I am asking legit like that was you I said
the Tommy Lee shit about yeah yeah yeah okay all right god your voice sounds so
much darker
I
Can you see my name
No, we don't see my son. He said, oh, there we go, psyche. Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh. You're a little, you know, you're like, you're early. You're either later early. I'm not, I don't know, but he's lots of Hayden later early.
Hayden, do you hate me or love me today? Hey, God, are you gonna unblock me or what God?
He unblock me so I can post that you in the chat
Monica are you lost
I'm going to try right now. I
didn't see the chart. Yeah.
Monica, you're taking over the
panel, which is not going to
happen. I don't give up.
Go set up. Go. Thanks for letting
me off. It's a shut up. You're
inviting me like a couple of
weeks ago. So, here I am.
You just
Yeah
Blocked me and she talks crap
We don't care
I can go live right now and open my own panel. If you want to go live and open it, you don't
fuck where you're here. Monica, go do it. I dare you. Go do it. Go do it. I'm finna
You let these fucking retards on here, and they fucking crash out
This is retarded
I
Bring my brawn down and then I start talking
We can all got it got it got it got it. Why are you got it? Why are you bringing drunk stances to my panel?
Well, what are you doing?
He's out there I don't think he's a real Santa Claus. I don't think you have a resemblance
Hold it down. I want to know if I'm on a naughty or nice list. Oh my god
Santa
you anywhere else and I'd be like, that's Santa.
Oh, he's flexing, he's flexing, he's flexing, he's flexing.
Can you take over the shirt?
Can you flex your shirt?
Can you flex your shirt off of the hose?
You look good for, that's pretty good Santa play.
Oh yeah, there we go.
pull up the shirt, pull up the shirt to the shoulder, pull up the shirt to show him the muscles
You've got if you've locked it. Should I blow it out? Should I blow it? See this guy'd be on the bed. No, I mean, he's
If God, you're not gonna burn them up so easily. He's faster on the computer than he is
Hey, hey Santa, can I sit on your lap? Can I sit on your lap for Christmas and tell you my wishlist?
Oh, okay, so it's like that's actually talking to me, right? He wants. Yeah, you want you to bounce him on his knee?
I'll go easy. What do you want?
You got you got work for Christmas working arms. Oh, that's a sight and him
I just I just want everyone to be happy in your office and everyone to be happy bro
You you did this shit off you you don't understand what the fuck you but that's all right
But he also but he is a dumb dumb man in that movie he was a dumb dumb correct
Just fucking, just a drunk old motherfucker trying to flex on the camera.
I've never dated anyone for a million, a million dollars.
He's, yeah.
Peace out, peace being here, thank you.
Thanks for joining, now we're gonna go with the New Yorker.
People like Bonnetville will try to convince you
I'm a cut of boys.
Now we're gonna go with the New Yorker.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Bye Santa, see you next year Santa, bye.
You go up here you dumb fuck.
I don't know, I don't know.
I don't know, I don't want to say it, I don't want to say it.
That wasn't very, yeah, thank you, this was my panel.
The minute he said he was involved with Ghost,
I woulda kicked him.
Okay, oh really cuz I joined way more than you you don't fuck what you'd like to talk about it
I can actually defend myself
I'm smarter than I'm smarter than you I know that I can actually be myself
You come up here and you ruin the fucking panel. I come up here and have a nice conversation like we did have before
I just copied your fucking
Whose panel make the argument English brother not New York you got to speak English no, I'm talking to you. You're talking to me, right?
And I've been joining this panel for the past like two years
Where the fuck are you talking to me? Let's have an action park.
Get me live for two years.
This is where I live for it.
Saki, please let me have this debate. Let's run it.
I
Don't I don't know I think she was like she's saying I should show support
I don't know if she's live right now. Hey guys go say hi to beta. You know who the fuck care. She's crying again
I have to pay nobody cares. You're talking to me
Well, you're talking to me
Don't disrespect the most people person on his fucking I've been up here for like a
Long run up here like 45 minutes. I think
Join you fucking disrupt everything you see where the problem is right?
We're good everyone's good
All I said was that like I just thought if it is not okay, then we should all go support her because she supports us
I'm fucking you know what I mean
I'm just gonna make sure she's good because I don't like when any of you hurt and I don't want to know if anybody's not doing good
You know, I support both I support both of them. You know, I
Psychies be the best friend. I was fucked up so I support
I don't know. I don't. I don't
know. I don't know. I don't know.
I'm just I'm just telling you the truth psyche. Yeah, I was good
I was on a panel for like two hours already just now and it was cool tonight. I'm just saying he was cool
I don't think he's gonna spell out who gives a fuck. It's not his animal
Are you bring this? Who cares? Oh my god
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Shut up. That's my brother. We were having a good panel page page. Were we not having a good panel?
We're not all getting along
Psyche Psyche Psyche take it off page. Let's talk to you. We're not having a good panel. We're all getting along
Was that fun?
Everything is fine. Everything is fine guys. Let's all come down. Yeah, it's not
Am I the only person we stream this I get yet with anybody else
You're the one that brought these people over but I think goes to be stream
Go to more and it says re-stream go to more and it says
And it goes on your page
Yeah
I'll just make a video on your channel if you guys would like to
Yo, can you hear me? Can you hear me?
It's coming to clear. Everything's coming to clear.
No, we can't. We can't hear you.
Pidge, Pidge, Pidge, Pidge.
Pidge, you can always stop it. You can always delete it if it's too much, but yeah.
Everything's fine. Everything's on fire, right?
Okay, okay. Okay. Okay. My check. My check. One two. My
check. Don't don't. You don't have that. Just don't have it.
You can just know that it's an option. It's an option in the
future. If you want to like have your audience see you on
the show. If I put it on now, you got Blahopalmer. No, it'll
see from right now. Okay, then no. Okay. Okay. Yeah, you
Blahopalmer. Blahopalmer, stay till we hear you. I'll just I'll
Everything is fine
No, don't accept the bait. No, I could hear you the whole time
Yeah, I'll take the bait though. Yes. Yeah selective hearing. Yeah, I heard what I wanted to
Oh, what's happening?
Every so much going on.
I don't know.
They've let, Pidge, he let them in.
It's obviously gonna be like this.
Well
You want to let me out simple as that
Like what I was saying
Drop me on the back and be like you're in no way you don't know what the fuck you're talking about
You shouldn't be up here. You ruin the panel
You don't have to join a friendly panel you don't have to be friends
Would you like me to keep crashing out and keep going?
Cause I'll do it.
I'm coming in clear.
You're not going to answer to me, are you?
Yo, easy.
Stop manipulating.
Yo, yo, yo.
I'm doing it.
I'm in this game, buddy.
Yo, yo, yo.
Fuck you.
How many times can I ask him to hear you?
How many times are you gonna ask if we can hear you?
I don't think that's a problem, but we were just sitting there talking about we were just sitting there talking about wigs and everybody's yelling and debating
No, I rage bait, but I'm not even good at it. You guys took it
You're here to be a retard
Talking about hair wigs, like I ain't here to debate.
Oh, shit.
That's what you want.
Don't make me go next door.
Keep saying that. Go next door. Go next door, dumbass. Go.
Actually, go three times.
No, go go go and then come back. I'm gonna go come back
Go go six times and then come back. You don't got shit on me. Go and then come back
I don't give a fuck when you say you're gonna you're not gonna have shit on me. You were like that, right?
I don't give a fuck where you go. I'm gonna fuck how many times you're going go
You're still gonna have the fucking same still mass argument. You're not gonna ever defeat me go wherever you want go to heaven, bitch
So I wonder if we can start with the next story and see how that works.
Paige, come back on Paige.
Paige, that was insane, I'm sorry Paige.
I think everybody can reach out.
I try to keep it cool, psyche, but if people come at me, I gotta shoot back.
No, you don't.
No, I don't.
No, don't give them the fucking satisfaction.
You know your yo chat is at is 125 yo shout out to the chat y'all right quick
I don't everybody I looked and that was it. I'm not coming back until unless
So, I'm not coming back unless you guys stop fighting and yelling over each other, dumb shit, because I'm not in a good time.
Alright, I got you, Paige. I respect you.
Good page, Lee.
Oh yeah.
I'm a little mad, she left.
No more, no more, okay, I got you, I got you, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got you baby, I got
And it's not even me.
He's talking about somebody else.
You're a plan.
I see what you do.
You try to burn it up to people while I sneak this in the next man and act like you're the
victim.
I see what you do, family.
I see right through you.
You butter them all. Oh such and such. Oh they trying to ruin the channel. Oh watch out. They're gonna pull them all over you.
They're trying to have a good time.
Nobody's here for none of that. Nobody's here for none of that.
So full back and stop using the fake ass, fake ass manipulation technique.
They're not gonna work.
There we go
Need it
Yeah, you're a good boy. Let's go.
Hey, hey, man.
Oh, my God, that house feels amazing.
Scotto, I said hi to you.
I don't know if you heard me, though.
Yo, chat. What up, chat?
Yeah, I'll dance to you to chat in a minute.
Let me go to the chat.
You look up.
W to the chat.
Yeah, ready to know.
Respect to y'all, yo.
Yo, chat, chat, always wins.
Oh, that's what you need to see.
Marsha knows the chat always wins.
Hey, man, how you doing?
Off-office.
Yo, listen, I made mistakes in my past,
and everybody knows it by now.
And I regret most of it, but you can't pick out a bear
and just make the bear to be peaceful.
Leave me alone.
Let me live my nature life.
I'm going to light some prayer candles as well.
I'm going to wash myself on live with the water
floor last year, the floor of the water.
Good get it and get you little demons
I'm lighten up my archangel Michael
candle
And then I also got a rice crispy treat one you feel better putting me backstage you feel better
I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I
the
Do you want it? We can fucking run it. Let's go. Let's run that mode. Nobody's even talking to you. It goes. Nobody's talking to you
You're too stupid to have the coverage. I wasn't talking to you
I'm gonna drop down on the back tables like not hushed enough. Thank God you brought these retards over at night
You're gonna drop them. I didn't bring any retards over. You're worse than the retards
You brought them over you're worse
Fucking crack it
Rubbing baby oil on it. You're not to run your channel brother
What the fuck is this?
Those look like a fucker.
We got a crack in here, we got a crack in my pants.
What the fuck is this?
Hey y'all stop playing with me.
Y'all open your eyes.
He's a mellow, my lord.
I'm not that light.
He looks like a balloon.
What the fuck is going on tonight?
I'm about to sign off.
This shit is crazy.
Saki, you gotta control your panel, brother.
I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I
Take away the evening. First of all, you're not letting people have fun. Second of all, you're not letting them debate. So what the fuck are you doing?
Just destroying everything?
It's either you have fun or you debate. I mean, I don't know.
Listen, guys, he's singing this Crackhead prayer.
Hey, what's up, man? I don't know.
Crackhead prays to his Crackhead God.
Isaiah! Isaiah!
Isaiah!
What's up, brother?
What's up, what's going on, bro? Oh, hey, Paige. Are we back? I don't know
But no, we're not psychies in control. Oh, no, no. All right. All right. Well, psyche. Are you in control?
I'm bad at control, but it's not funny. What's up, buddy?
Are you ready to go away? You want to go? You want to be kicked out by talking back to me?
No, let him up. One by one on the big old one. What's funny?
I don't want to debate. I don't want to debate show.
What would you let them ruin your fucking I mean I'm just confused I guess my bad because you're gonna kick your butt out of the suit just get out of this for just smiling
You're gonna kick me and not them?
Yeah I'm gonna kick you
Go, go, go, go, go, just smile, just smile
Everyone says don't kick me but you're gonna kick me
I will, I will, I will
You know what, I'm smiling
I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I'm smiling I
We're causing the drama and we don't want drama. We never thought I'd talk about passing you
Ghost let's all come everyone just have a deep breath
But if y'all listen to him, all he does is say the word debate a hundred times
I'm saying debate a hundred thousand times, but you never have enough
Just bring up a topic bring up a topic
Guys
I'm gonna really fucking kids come in and my blood is a little bit boiling
Think of her volume psyche to 200 cuz she's
Now I just do some agua water on me. I feel good
Praise got the stage going psyche get the stage going. Thank you. Marsha's little candle
Amen. Amen. Whoever got he brought baby all your lawn him
He feels good. He's waiting for the next man to get behind him. You heard
Who are you talking about me?
No, no, no
Yes, I did
That sounds like a man right there. You just say your hands are fucked. That sounds like a man
If you don't have calluses you're doing it wrong
right
I've got calluses from holding the scissors and comb
Thank you page. Thank you, Marcy. Thank you everybody
Thank you everybody
When I light prayer candles, I say the prayer and I leave them lit until they go out.
I saw me get the Father's Son Holy Spirit.
I could get it in front of y'all.
Father's Son Holy Spirit, take this evil wave in me.
Know the evil, be blessed, and God got my back.
And God will always have my back. Amen.
The real God.
Who the fuck is your God, Lucifer?
That's who you're born to?
Who you pray to Eli you you know, you pray to lose
Thank you, thank you
It's a no-question. You been your night
My oh you sound so good. You sound you sound retarded
Why would a man pray to another man like at least make sense
What's the name under your name? Stay tuned the people's podcast you pray to illa. Let's go
That just that's just there under my name. I never changed. I never
Like I never put it there. I never put it there. They put it there when I came to change
Apparently, I gotta
Put the tattoo on my shirt. We're gonna fight against evil. So you I put the tattoo on my shirt you are
Bet you see it though. You see it. You see it
Why you mad
I'm made for psyche and positive energy
I say that man say that stop talking. I can tell you why I'm mad if you don't mind
I'm mad because you guys came up here and ruined the fucking panel
You know what the fuck you're talking about at all you have here having a good-ass time
We were laughing you guys came up here and tried to ruin it, but what are you trying to ruin it with let's fucking run it
Today any of you dumb dumb
We were having a good-ass panel we ever a good-ass panel, but I'm gonna refrain from arguing
All right, then why would you join you fucking retard? Let's run that bitch dog. Why would you join?
Let's run it. Let's argue. Let's debate
Why do you feel like you feel like
Why do you feel like you felt the need to join the panel and ruin that shit? Why?
I didn't feel the need to join the panel ruin it. I see what you did. You did join
that need
I'm psyche is live. So I left me. I don't know what's ever. I don't know if anyone
How about that? That's the real reason I'm asking you who wants it and then like 24 hours later
You're gonna
Let's run that bitch
I just ran it yeah
I mean I can't make an order for my brother, but let's just say the like I'm letting you know
I wouldn't let you up dumb dumb. Why would I let you up ma'am? Why wouldn't I let you up?
Listen, you can't accept the truth for what it is. I'm yeah, let's run it was shit
It's not a fucking answer shit. Let's run that bitch. Let's debate about it. Let's go
Let's debate about it. What do you mean by shit? What does shit mean?
You're gonna say shit the burden of proof is gonna be on you dumb dumb
We're having a good fucking panel, let's run it
You lost an argument now you're saying bye. No, let's run that bitch dog
Yeah, come get it check the score. Let's run it
No, no, no check the score. Let's run that bitch. What do you mean?
No, no, no, no, you're not gonna talk anymore cause I'll burn you up, dude
Would you like to go ahead with your argument?
No, you're gonna listen listen you guys do not understand the whole point of the fucking stage two seconds in are we children?
You're gonna go right fucking back at each other get a grip or I'm fucking out
She has broken we are all pulling up. No, I got her back fucking out. Fuck it. I have pages back
Who wants to run it? Exactly. We're all fucking it's not a chill chat when you join your fucking retard. Let's run that bitch dog
No, yeah, when you're here, you're not chill
You're not chill
Then stop arguing stop talking let page talk. Yeah, it's their channel correct page page
You're not gonna send a whole fucking people. Let's fucking run that bitch dog
You're too stupid to have the conversation. You're trying to fucking argue when you don't know the fuck or like you could back
Yeah, I'm gonna say to be fair. You don't go if you came back like an asshole
I
Came back like the back door. So other way though
Yeah, I know I just look up and I was like hey
Marcy stop let me handle this real quick
But let us handle that like we don't care about your input. Let us handle it. Well. Yeah, okay. That's our own problem, correct?
Handle somewhere else. You're the one that join you dumb fuck you join. It's our problem. You join
Is it really that hard to defend? It's like it's our problem
It's our problem you dumb fuck. All right, let's run out fucking debate anybody who wants to run it
Me and Paige are going to Isaiah's I don't know what you guys are doing man. Thank you so much
I was about to comment. Thank you so much you man. I'll leave it play copyrighted music here
All right fuck this shit
200 I cannot hear you
Hey, do you got to stop answering I'm trying to have a page you got to shut up
Can't hear
Hey, Maya, how are you? Hey, man? Jamie's Cowboys
Under thank you to Decker Kung Fu Manchu for being a member. Hey guys, how are you?
Guys guys
First of button
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm
Let's run it. We were having fun, dude.
Let's run it.
I'm saying let's run it. Get me. Yeah, put me full screen. No, put me full screen.
Put me full screen, please.
There you go.
Put me full screen. Let's run that.
Put me full screen.
No, I'm the debater. Put me full screen.
I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I don't believe it. I
Unless you get
Yeah, I love Florida walk I didn't see
What is going on so much anger
for nothing. Oh, I don't know. Where is it? Where is it? Where is it? Oh,
little friends. Oh, one more time. One more time. Alex is going to join. Alex says he's
going to join. Right, Marcy? Yeah, he'll do it. He's going to join. Alex, Alex, where are
you? You let them ruin your show.
Well, no
My show ruined. Oh, you know, they just okay. Say one more thing. Say one more thing. I don't like
You don't like me why don't you like me? No, no, I like I like you say what say one more thing
Say one more thing. I don't like me. Say one more thing. I don't like them ruining your show
Okay
Yeah, I blocked him permanently.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Fuck that motherfucker.
I don't know.
It wasn't me.
I think it's camera cut out or something.
I'm so sorry.
Okay.
So, hi everybody.
How's everyone doing?
What's up, psyche?
Hi.
Oh my god, you were like early morning. So I'm glad. I know
I'm different times than today. Oh my gosh. You fell off. You
fell off. You know, I saw 47 48 now 40 people to chat. So I'm
doing okay. Can we get a fucking reading? I'm in California
too, honey. So I'm like three hours behind everybody else as
well. Don't worry, psyche. I'm doing a world tour around the
world. You never know if I'm like, psyche, come outside.
I wanted to be a stepdad too.
If you come to California, you definitely have to pick me up
and then we'll go down and hang out with Psychi.
I'm doing a world tour.
I'm a world tour.
We walk on a pier.
We'll get the best fish chocolate,
or we'll get some other seafood.
Too bad.
You know, all right.
I'm going to send myself to a rat.
Have you ever been to the neighborhood church there, Psychi?
Yeah.
I grew up right there. That was my church. That was my church
My mom grew up in Palsford even with like any time we'd go visit my grandma
We used to go there that place is safe, dude. Yeah, I like I was actually right down the street from there
I went to that school Malik Malikov school was right right there in the area, too
And I went to that school. I was that was the prep school for I went there for seven years and
And so yeah, and the Palisbury states has peacocks. It has it's a magical place
It has it has the ocean it has
It was next to what used to be the goalie. I don't know if you remember that in Palace Rides Rancho Palace Rides
Before you got to the supermarket
Like in in town if you kept going down
But yeah, my mom grew up there
I'm talking about guys it was there was a really rich dude that built this basically like Earth's castle. It's like a really nice
Classically you like done home. It's got a huge, hold on, a huge organ.
I
There's there's like a there's like a checkerboard like the outside my actually my brother got married there and I used to go there
I was a youth group for that church, and we also would do like these Halloween's there
Well, there'd be the scariest Halloween and it was a mansion
so people would just go room to room with this mansion and it was a mansion was a church and
Yeah, when the guy died he left it to
to the church to use, and so it's just massively badass out.
But it's got like, what was it like 1920s era?
Well, yeah, because the city was founded.
I mean, there's a whole interesting story
about the city was like founded.
Also, the city has no stop lights,
has no, it's every house has a red roof.
It's all the, and they had these famous architects
come down to design all the houses.
There's a flanked wood right there down there.
and I also went to school right on the on the beach it was like basically it was my cliffs you
walked down it's about us yeah my grandma um i don't know if you remember when the gully was there
they like uh
If you were going down it's before you get to Marine World or any of that
They built the house there and my grandpa works for Lockheed and
And it was in the family all the way until 2003
I
Been around me that's what it means
What give a couple days off saggy's and then I came back
Hey, I can't hear a word you said I saw your lips
So, yeah, I know Isaac is doing home. I was gonna show tricks. Hey, Jamie. What's the Trix?
Oh page can't yeah, I can't hit page she's talking
Oh, you're muted. You're muted page. I can't hear your page.
Aww. Aww.
Where's my dotty? I have one called dotty that has similar marking, almost exact same margin actually.
Twins.
Do you have twins?
If you don't mind if I ask do you have one that that's called dumb and the other one called
No, no, no. Yeah, just so you
Ghosts I've been digging for your balls when it went one is named dumb and the others named up and that's where balls are called
One's got great
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm
There's a weird laugh. Who wants to who wants to run it? Oh, yeah, well, hey, I'll be good ghost now you chase page away
Hey
Chase page
We were literally having a good time
Literally having a great time. No
I might be in a chair
Well, you're gonna have to ask page then
You're going to make that claim burden to focus on you ask page. Who's me Allie? This goes to reason why you left ask her.
I love you. It's okay. I love me. I love you.
You're going to have to ask page to burden to focus on you. It's not that hard.
No, my audio wasn't working. Yes. That was weird. Can you hear me now? Can you hear me? Yeah, we can hear you now. Okay, then we're good. Then we're good. I just had to clear it clear with my audio up. I don't know why that's working.
Everybody gets paranoid. Hello. Don't leave me. That's not everybody gets paranoid. We're trying to get some happy shit. The fuck are you doing this for?
You don't. You don't. You don't.
You don't. You don't.
So I see hello. Hello. Are you there LES are you there?
Lower east side
Can we talk or not
Thank you, James. I know I'm the best
You know a lot of people talk when you shouldn't I understand that's hard
You need some help brother and I'm here to help you
And I got your back one of the one person that had your back got you like
That's not fair to say. I was back to you
Pretty neutral with everybody
I got pages back all day long
We're trying to have fun though if you want to debate
So what should we do? Nobody's cock-blocking. They're starting to cock-block you fucking retard.
He's just crazy.
Oh, I'll take a crash out.
I love those right sides, man.
Remember when it was such a nice piano?
Yeah, look at, look at, remember?
Remember the good old days?
Yeah, right.
Good old days.
I remember.
Like that holiday.
Aww, see I tried, not happenin'.
Just remember I was there for you.
You guys were all there, we were all there for each other.
Now it's that, okay? What are you doing? What are we gonna do?
What do you want to do?
I'm gonna go if you don't want anything.
I should do a reading on my fucking own channel one day and just like being here with everybody else
And I don't want it I can do panels, but I don't want to do panels yet. Yeah, yeah
Everybody's good everybody's really been helpful and everything, but I still kind of don't know if I want that
Yeah
Kind of lame when you're sitting there like we're kind of like just talking to yourself
But you're talking to the chat like you're not by yourself. Wait, it's awkward. Yeah, it's super awkward
You kind of have a moment for you pause and you're like cool
Right, yeah, that's a good show
How come how can we keep leaving and coming back with no no one to crash it. I'm sick
Can I not join this page? Why was saying I was sick remember when I joined you were having a lot of fun. Yeah, I was having a lot of fun
I know
Yeah
You can always have fun
Have a new fun now a different kind of
New fun
I'm down for it. I'm down for it.
Pages good broad and our horizons.
Well, I'm gonna try what like my soul, like my son, beer, is the nectar of the gods.
No shit. So I'm here. Nah. Can't we get
What's the next episode of Gods? Stop playing with me Paige. Oh my fucking god
Will you play unless you want to run it? I'm the debater. I'm the debater here. You want to run it?
Let's run that
You can't answer it
What do you want to hear we're hanging out
I'm gonna be the person
I'm gonna be the person that's telling you the truth.
Everyone shut the fuck up.
This shit is getting fucked.
We're not gonna shut the fuck up.
Goddamn, so you left this fucking panel under shit.
Hey, talk.
I still want them to fight.
I don't want to talk.
Exactly, and Paige has spoken.
Oh, you want us to fight?
Yeah, go ahead.
Go ahead. Please fight. I want you to fight.
Go ahead.
Is that reverse psychology? Does that work?
Don't give a fuck you just don't want to hear it right now when I will leave soon, and then you guys seem to everyone
I just want to have fun over here. Okay
Everyone's going through a hard time. Let's just not make it worse, right? Yeah
Let's have this be enjoyable and fun for everybody not just any party at all. It's one-sided
I haven't read the chat in a while. Let's do that. Let's take a break
Yeah
Right what have you guys not to do tonight?
Well, I've currently having what happened before I came
I'll have that party with you.
Yeah.
Make it.
I
Have one of those lights like
No, it's the PCP baby. I'm getting naked
What kind of charger does it take like a USB or is it like when it's a little baby a lighter
So it looks like this and it's a speaker. It's called blue
And it's that's cool. Yeah, it's like does a disco ball shit like kids
But we can play some beats in it too, but you can also just use the lights
I think oh wow you can play beat in it, and then it goes to the beat, right?
You can play beats in it? Say what?
You have to follow the clues to fight it every time
Every day's a scavenger, huh?
Yeah, I'm trying to find something to play music on it got shit my other phone sticks
Oh my god
You gotta turn off all your lights page. How much does it take like 50 flicks?
No, it's probably only like three or four
She would like the light the light the light the left the left the left again, okay
One flick to rule them all
I can't find it. Power off.
Well.
Well, how you leave? Oh, he got
in and out services. I can't
find a charger for it. So, we're
going to have to just not do it
right now. It wasn't meant to
be. Oh, Lord, it wasn't meant
to be. Oh, Lord, she said, hold
on, baby. Let's go. Let's go
Hey, I'm gonna hit you with the Alex. I'm gonna hit you with the Alex. So you can come back?
This is why you don't give up because you can
Your list of page one of my one of my one of my motivations pieces never give up never something
I'm not gonna get a block though for it.
My daughter, my daughter looks at me when I say that.
She's like, daddy, I know, I know.
Never give up.
Fucking hell.
Never surrender.
Oh, it's just a tiny cord.
Tricks, snakes, everything.
Okay.
It needs to charge for just a second.
What are you doing?
What are you calling me?
Is that not the charger for it either?
Oh, it's just bent.
I think.
He's like, let me down, let me down, baby.
Okay, it just needs to charge for like a second or so.
Cool, baby. Just a second. Leave, please. Leave, please.
Stop talking. Don't talk over me. You know better. You heard I am the king leave page alone
And by the way, you're never gonna defeat him if you're gonna do it do it. You're not gonna do it are you?
too much of fucking retard even out of the conversation leave page alone leave me alone
shut the fuck up so I'll burn all you I sound like Marcia I'll burn your ass up Marcy maybe
you should check the score and Marcia you're a dumb fucking dumb bitch for bringing these
people over here
Fucking retarded by the way
Thank you
We need a piece of panels like you had a piece panel they didn't need to bring drama, but I broke I broke people
Yep
Man I slept weird on my neck
Those lights, we need Isaiah up here because that's the way the page door of the lights because Isaiah had his, why the fuck he back now, why he left?
Page door, now I like page lights now. Well, thank you, raise your lights. Thank you put on your lights
You Isaiah, that's what you should have on page right now. You Isaiah and your page
There you go now psyche turn on your lights and get up in this motherfucker and all three
y'all go on the bottom or the top whatever one you want to put it and get the party going
I
Like
Yeah, I am who I am in person in real and online in real life. So like you have a great time with me
No, we're each other likewise
Make the argument go ahead
It's a rare you don't know the fuck you're talking about sir. I fucking win
Yo, you couldn't even do that right you heard him he said
What's it? What's it? What's it do?
Yeah, it's because it was so beige.
How you pulling the lights and then blocking the camera?
I'm so disappointed.
Marcy, where's your lights?
Oh, I know.
Marcy, I don't got lights.
I don't got lights.
I'm sorry, y'all.
Marcy, where's your lights?
Lights.
Marcy, you got lights?
Let's go. It's the light party. Yo, thank you. Keep me out. Come up. I'm going to do what I like. I'll wait. I'll wait to plug in the book.
Come up. Come on. Thank you. Come back. Thank you. Come back. Put your lights on.
I can't really see it. I got these ones. Am I going to make these ones fast enough for you guys to see?
Maybe not.
Might look like Christmas lights.
I like it. I like it. You got red on one side and blue on the other.
They're just like, I need to figure it since this is fucking something going on over here.
It's just doing everything it wants to do. I don't know how to work at it right now. It's dark.
Just leave it.
Isaiah got, he got like 3,000. He got master likes 3,000.
Yeah, he's got the fucking
Mine is like the wall mine is like the Walmart version of his like
Oh, oh, this is a Walmart fucking light bulb. It just kicks out everybody's
That's it it's just a it's a screw-in fucking light bulb. Well, it's like a weird two-ended spitty contraption, but
It's not from Walmart. It was just like a like it was just like comparison as to the quality of how cool kids is compared to mine.
Yeah, these are.
Okay, okay.
I'm a little drunk. I'm a little drunk.
Like this go yeah, I'm mad. I don't know how to use the show y'all right now. I'll be like
You got two two and a half minutes, let's run that bitch you got two and a half minutes go ahead
We got two minutes to be but what do we go ahead two minutes for
Not talking you got two minutes for two inches
No, yeah, let's run it you got two and a half minutes. Let's run that bitch
Two minutes for two minutes two minutes for two and a half inches. It's okay. Well now you got two minutes
All right, keep going. What is this one? Oh, that's what it is when it goes faster. I think
Alright, now you got a minute and a half. Now you got a minute and a half. Go ahead.
It was well spent.
I got five on it.
Oh, David Cowboy got us all.
That's why you got ten viewers. Alright, you got a minute and a half. Run that bitch.
What are we doing, Ghost? What do you mean?
Can someone answer me? Why are you guys ignoring me?
Are you getting a backstage?
They can't get along
Well, if you want to join the panel you can get along, okay?
Yeah
Look me and Marcia. You're cool. We're just chilling. Why do you guys we're not fighting over stupid shit?
I don't think we don't fight with nobody
My god, you're running around the kitchen like fucking mad. It's like mad. I was in here
Marcy huckers so tan you look like you're ten seconds brother you're gonna run it
God hey ghost wins again motherfucker. I'm long defeated check the score. I'm undefeated
Hey, I fucking run this bitch dog, and I'm talking to shit right now. Anybody wants to come check me come check me
I don't know what to check
I don't know either.
But these kittens are going crazy.
I can hear their little bells in the back.
Yeah.
My husband's like, oh, they like the bell one.
So he went and he bought a whole bag of them.
I'm like, oh, my God.
Bell madness.
They have 100 toys.
Yeah.
I'm like, you can roll up a plastic bag.
He was earlier this morning when the kittens went outside.
One of them was playing with the rock
And I was like, see you need to go and get the choice where I'm going to take out a rock plastic bag. Oh, I'm back. I'm back. Oh my God. I didn't even notice I was back.
What are you playing musical assholes? Like what's happening here?
Literally, seriously, I don't, I have no idea. I just keep getting back room.
Well.
I'm not just randomly leaving.
Thank you, Sado.
Well, I've been offline like I haven't been online too much
Yeah
It seemed like I was only catching everybody because like
The time difference for everybody, you know, like I would always catch like me in the early morning, you know, like right before the panel and
So that's happened the last couple of days. Yeah, I'm glad I could be hitting them.
That's good. I'm glad you're feeling a little bit better, hunks.
I know this really takes a lot of the...
Well, Marcy and Paige, I got... Yeah, at the same time, it should be at 12 o'clock, right?
Like, 12.49?
No, it's 1.49 here.
It's 12.49.
She's one hour ahead.
All right.
Yeah.
That's like Colorado. Colorado's one hour ahead.
Are you like directly north of Colorado?
Do you guys not split your shit up all stupid like we do in America?
No, we split our shit up all stupid like you do in America when it comes to the fucking times like clocks like the yeah
It's it's fucking stupid
Like there's like so Nova Scotia
Well, it's Cape Breton is like that's far far east coast and so I'm in Alberta
But like so it's BC every province is different off like none of us have the same time in any of the provinces
No
Time difference is insane even just within within my own country. Yes
Yeah, and then it's like very similar or very much on point with some of your guys's
You know what I mean? It's pretty crazy
Yeah, so like if you go to one spot if you go to one spot if you drive if you drive to the place
There's our way and our change is still being our saying
No, not quite so like we'd have to drive another province over which is normally like a couple
It depends if you live an hour from the border of anywhere in each province and yeah
I guess your hour would switch just to drive but a province is like the state, right?
See actually I understand that question yet that no his question. Yeah, it's true. Yeah
and you drive an hour, it's the same time as when you left, yeah.
Exactly, when you're in the light of a light, in the light of a light, and it's like...
Three hours behind us in California. So
Hawaii it's a five-hour flight, but yeah, it's really only like that three hours. Yeah, it's a trippy. So like, you know
Yeah, like I had so much to say but then I don't want to say it. So I'm not gonna say it anyways. Look at our lights. They're really cool
It would be one of those things where like people would just get used to it getting dark at
whatever o'clock, right?
But what do you think, Marcy?
Like, what do you think it would be trippy if you lived an hour from the border
and you had to go over the border and it was just only an hour away?
Then when you got there, you're like, your mother fucking has to be stuck in time
or not wasting any literally or not even in it.
Like, it's just weird to think about it because it's like,
you're there at the same time when you fucking left.
You know what I mean?
Right.
Time is a social construct.
Like, you're just skipping time, just playing it,
just like a fiddle.
Time to travel.
Yeah, crazy.
I think it's confusing. It's very confusing. That's the thing. I think it's cool, but you know what?
The only people... It's interesting though. It's interesting. It's very interesting.
The only celestial beings on this whole, this whole universe that try to fucking control time
or even calculate it is us. And it's because our physical expires. It has an expiration date.
so they're forget to calculate some kind of time frame to give or to see do you know what I mean
what I'm trying to say but everywhere else linear it doesn't exist just like money only has value
because we give it money otherwise it's just paper right yeah we give it we give a value we give
so really does like anything exist if we don't like it's I don't know we're not
getting into it we don't give nothing about you does it doesn't mean does it
have any value no it doesn't unless it has to have value to like you as a
person but that's still the same fucking thing is giving it meaning and why it
has value to you as you it means something to you right anyway and then
once we see that
Human reaction is to copy that person. Oh, that means dollars to that person. Let me do the same thing
right and it initially started with the elements like the gold
and you know all the
enriched minerals and
Oh
We were having a good time, but anyone wants some smoke. I'm down like you want to smoke weed with me
You want to like butt put do you want to like you want to like fight?
You want to fight that's what he means. You want to fight? Yeah
Nobody want to fight ghost, I'm sorry, you know, I really don't want to fight
Wait, are there are those ghosts? Yeah. Yeah, Arbiter's ghost
Dun dun dun
Excuse me. Those is our way. Uh, that was the stuck place of the year
It's okay page
I finally show face for people didn't believe I was who I was and that's why I did it
You heard it?
I heard what I said.
I didn't hear you.
I am this guy. This guy right here, this is me.
As you've seen today
When people have different names and different this and different that like this is this is me
I'm the most people Marcy. That's Marcy, but like
Yeah, I don't look around with that bullshitting. No
Playing oh, did you see my thing moved unless that's just me cuz I'm stoned. I thought it did maybe
Maybe it was me
Well, Jesus, I'm having a cough attack. Sorry guys
Can't wait for this to be done. Hey having a cold. Where is site click to heal you?
Psych ready I gotta head with the site you go. Hold on. Hold on. Everybody gotta hit on the Alex call psyche come back
Like you come back
It's yeah, be does or something like where do you go?
It's like
Is she live I told her to go live. I was gonna join by
We should probably go like be like on her life to go support her like if you don't come back. We all go on the beaters
I'm staying
I like when I go support Bita. She's my girl.
She knows we're there talking and listening.
That whole situation we're raising is crazy though.
I don't know I don't know about the drama. I tried to say it, but I'm just
Yeah, I said my opinion about it. I jumped on I look the reason I mentioned it because I dropped an opinion on it
And my opinion was it's not nobody for you to be mad at
Legion is case promoting it if Peter's promoting it your your fault lies against beater in yourself
Mean not be the I'm sorry. I keep on saying be the yeah, yeah, yeah, your fault lies against
flirty in yourself
And that's my opinion suppose that that's what I mentioned it
Oh, they're back with the party. I'll just look at my mind. Oh fuck. I don't know why I keep getting back door
I have no idea damn son. You could have been beating you meet and you you could have got exposed
Well, you know, I would all right
I would love to be doing something that cool to actually deserve getting put in the back room
But I can't say I did shit. I'm a boy or like that
Hi guys
Hello
page
Marcy
Marcy I'm back. Hi. How are you?
No, it's just so weird like I don't see the control over the people that get kicked off
I don't know it's not me guys. I think there's like a road mod or something. I'm kind of like
There's so many bad as someone other person
It's a secret. It's a secret
Yeah, don't worry about it. I mean don't be fine guys. They're lost somewhere in the maze
The guys have elaborate behind me. They don't know Jarrus from the Goblin King
They don't know
Yeah, babe with the power
Hey, Marcy Marcy have I done a reading for you lately?
No, you haven't I haven't joined the hood. You're from the south. Are you from the south or no?
Cuz we'll be but I have a so I have the Alice deck. I have a villain's deck. I have a hoodoo tarot
Do you want any of those three?
You said the hoodoo one. Yeah, yeah
Okay
So, this is easy actually got me this this deck all the easy back on he but he got me this deck. So, I'll let him back up
He's gonna behave himself
He's not gonna say weird things
He's not gonna have a key call with the what's his name?
I
Thank you, I hope you know I'm a big supporter of you, bro
I was on spectic, but then I was like, no, I really like this guy cool. I
Need to go to that shopping
One day after a fucking paint what like a
The other day you showed
When I have to keep you
Everyone back, but I just want to make sure it's going to give you a good reading
So you had the two of coins the two of coins you've been keeping things balanced
You've been keeping like something you've been making sure you've been there's been waves lately, but it's like you've been able to like
Keep it keep things balanced no matter what happens. You're always like
able to
See the other side always it just even even keying on it not extreme, right?
but this has to do with the
Earthly thing so it says the two of coins says
Two coins says
It says
The plant is seaweed and it says, a juggler rides a motorcycle or unicycle as a huge tidal wave rises in the background.
He has drawn a circle of protection around himself in the sand in hopes that all will be well in the end.
Meaning it has a well balanced life, having your priorities in the right order,
And so I think that's a talented group
That's awesome that was like really great. That's really right on actually
But then we have this for this poor basket, I think the four pinnacles and look
Oh, she's being offered like another basket and she's like, oh, oh, I don't even
She's like
Yeah, she's like no more baskets. She's like another basket. I know it's no other baskets. I didn't like it
Okay, so she says it says the plant is Bay
A young woman is being offered just one more basket after rudely rejecting the other three
It says, the NG cufflinks belong to Neville Goddard,
I think she's wearing some cufflinks,
who was one of the most important
and influential New Thought voices of the 20th century.
The New Thought movement emphasized the power
of positive thinking and the ability of the mind
to manifest whatever the seeker desired,
also referred to as law of attraction.
Neville claimed that his teacher was a turban black man
Tutored him in scripture and no more mysticism scabala in Hebrew
You thought philosophy was incorporated into many black American spiritualist churches. So this says revitalization
Meditation introspection and the endless stagnation. So I think there's like, you know
maybe you've had some offers and you've rejected some offers, but
There's another offer coming and maybe it's the one you waited for so don't just like this counter cuz there's been so many that
disappointments, but finally this daughter of sticks and I know I think you like this. This is like
Yeah, I don't feel like horses. Yeah, so there's she is our horse and she's just like hold it on
Six yeah
the daughter six listen wouldn't normally be the page page of a
page of wands
This is daughter six. Okay, so this is daughter six. It says the plants are
Venue Greek and garlic does the daughter of sticks is rearing up a horse in order to change directions
The flock of birds above
Forming an arrow indicate. This is the best course of action. Okay, so
This is I say some animal signs. You're gonna sign some animals, maybe
But the daughter of six is all about getting pumped up and get the job done and maintaining the high energy until the very end
On the positive side, she's passionate determined bold free-spirited
Charming revolutionary self-assured and left to travel on the negative side. She's hot tempered abusive
overly competitive insecure loud
boisterous, jealous to show off, habitual procrastinator in a reading, if she doesn't
represent a liberal person with these qualities, she represents these attributes. So I don't know
if that's you or if that's somebody else, but you know you want to work on those positive qualities,
you know.
But there's always a shadow side to the positive quality. That's why there's always a deposit in the negative
So that they kind of go together, you know, you just want to stay in the highest on the highest because you know
You have some power you can ride the horse you can lead the
Whatever it is
The cattle whatever
Oh my god, who said that?
I'm a girl
No problem. Anytime.
You're welcome.
All right. Thank you.
Yeah, that being the one with the lady with the basket.
That was trippy because I've been trying to like work on meditation and
Feed it outcome of my goal and work towards that so that was really that was crazy
That's really right on
How's everyone doing how are you easy you guys maybe I'll draw mercy in that but I have a whole collection of art
You really didn't affect me as much
So, I can't I can't. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
Yeah, we all have DJ likes for a whole.
DJ likes to see.
All right.
Thank you. I want you to show my picture again because I think that might be the darkest example of me.
Is Gaudi?
Do we know what Gaudi looks like? I don't know.
You have to take a photo.
We only prophesized your thinker.
Yeah
Why you make easy look rasta, too
Okay, that's JT, that's not me, all right, three.
Why does JT look like, I don't even know, like,
he looks like the ice king mixed with,
I got lit on fire and can't put it out
and a homeless guy.
That's Michael Zofsky, that's Michael Zofsky right there,
Michael Zofsky.
Oh, you're sassy.
You know what, time.
Your turn.
All right.
We're spunky.
Thank you.
I don't think I've met that one yet.
Come on, bro.
That's what I thought.
Let's go.
All right.
Where's Christine's dog?
You're Jamie's cowboys
Here's Alex Alex
I need a screenshot, I need a
a screenshot, I need a
I need a screenshot, I need
a screenshot, I need
Did you uh, here's I say you got a job Marcy you got a job Marcy
You got a job Marcy and Paige
Okay, and Isaiah to you can't forget about Isaiah
I
That's like him
Like it's like you about much better, right? You see mice. No, look at mice. Look at mice. Wait. I'm zippin on the
That's the same pity you drew. He's
I'm happy everybody got a good sense of human didn't take nine offensive on psyche's drawings
Oh here he is guys this is like it right
Identical identical look at these twins a twin
How you doing I
Don't know I
Love doing but you know, I'm pretty good because they got 20 members. It's past couple days summer. Thank you so much
Shout out to everybody that's just cried. Thank you. Thank you very much. Thank you. Yes
Yeah, yeah, and he was the end of this earlier this year. I was like, you know, 10 people earlier this year
First day. Oh, no one wants no one likes you anymore. I want to come here anymore
Get up to 40 people 40 people. It's fine
Okay, so yes, and then Jamie think it was a super chat money for 20
My sake you Picasso. Oh, yeah, you like that money for 20 year anybody wants to once I'll send the drawing over
You want to draw? Oh
You trying to say you tired to thank you
No, it's over
Brian right now. I'm trying to use the government is a common the panel. I want to add you talk to personally Brian to
I've seen them both of these food is that I gotta go y'all
Easy, you know, I know you're straight, but you don't you run boo, you know, thank you
Love you all. Have a good night
Can I stop getting back door now fuck back room? I know I it's not it's not me. I have a I have the
Secret person and your mod is your mod is racist
They can't get it back
I'm sorry, you know, it's not me. I say it's not me. I
Have a secret mod and you can't you gotta fend that you keep offending them. I'm sorry
You're pissing them off
Yeah, oh, yeah, so how are you? How are you guys doing?
chilling
You're still me too
Okay
You want to come up tonight, I don't know the shows like you know the show is always the guests, you know the show which was the guest
And so you want to get a good guess, but I
Think I have a good guess
No, you're always good Marcy is like
I mean, I was men they keep
Buying for attention, why does I say keep getting food. I don't know Maya
I think I have
We have to ask the powers to be.
Yeah, there's several.
There's a lot of people.
Manifest ideas.
Because they're getting.
Panels.
Ready.
I say it.
Well, I say I shouldn't start on panel because he's already saying.
Hey, let's let's get out of here. Let's our own panels. You should sort of the panel. Thank you. I am the hearing impaired guy
I made you draw my head cuz a big goatee
Muscle cuz I'm a blacksmith. Oh, you are
Brian
Well, Brian sings the blacksmiths when I'm saying I would like to talk to him about some something I
Trust us
I'll I say I don't know
It's not but it's the guy. It's not DJ lecture. I have another secret person
They they're running my streamer. I'm too drunk for my streamer. Yeah, so um, they're running it
So I can't control this. I can't I can't I literally I cannot
Do anything right now
Whatever the whoever they want on they want on okay, they're like but they're kind of like my evil twin
So I can't really like
can't really control them okay I'll sub what's your channel I say I say you
let Ryan know I say it type in the oh you just put your channel name I say it
it's okay it gets you crazy crazy people and then all these all these games
Brian I got
Just give the name I see a food channel yeah, go ahead. I say I say you're once it in the chat
Go hang out in the chat I see
Going on the chat
Marcy, how are you?
I'm doing good. I'm laughing at my daughter. She just wanted to kiss me and kiss it on the head.
She's like, why do these cats smell so good?
They do. Oh my gosh. Well, like Lenore smells so good.
She's like, it's better than dog smells. Dog smells like weird, but
It's just because cats are pretty clean animals.
Yeah, they have a certain bacteria in them.
That is actually their clean bed.
Yeah, the more you know.
Because everything, if you think about it, is covered in some sort of bacteria.
Yep.
You can't escape it.
Here, here, I know.
Shit
Holy shit, holy fuck I got a lot back up. I
I got
demodded and
my fucking
My subscribed badge was removed too. I don't fuck happen
Wasn't he modded too couldn't post for a minute
Oh
I'm sorry
Ain't no thing about the wrenches. I thought you were dealing with a bunch of drama about fucking wrenches
That's why I had a teacher draw
I don't know if I should it's you before
It says where's my wrench in the feeding?
This is where I want to come in. Wait, where's my wrench? Where's my wrench?
So we were doing panel volleyball almost three years ago now
Like as a joke, we would always say that right? Well people would always say that so I had Acer draw me
I wears my wrench and before I even had to do the logo for my YouTube page
but
She gets that on a t-shirt, right?
It's a good where's my wrench on a t-shirt when you pass people that watch YouTube, but no
Yeah, I mean all I've done on this channel is like I was like I'll just be
The best version of myself. I'll be generous. I'll be loving. I'll be kind of I won't
Certify with anybody. I'll be nice to everybody. I
Just want to see if I'm just very nice
If I'm kind if I let everybody do what they want to do will happen
And a lot of it turned out to be though to try to walk all over me
They'll try to take advantage of me. They'll try to get one up on me. They'll try to slander me
You know, it's a this is really this
But the channel is really all a test
All I want to do is I just want to see
I'm gonna see who's gonna be honest with me. She's gonna tell me things
At this point, I've already been through all of it.
Anything to this point has been.
Everything's already been done 20 years ago, whatever.
It's like, right now, I'm just trying to find out who's going to tell me the truth.
So far, nobody.
Thank you, Jim.
Perfect.
He 420 found as yeah good good. Did I say it's channel morning for it's rain?
If you have a little bit left I've some left of my
What is it? It's like a it's a macaroni cheese sandwich. It's really good
My daughter thinks that sounds good.
Where'd you get the sandwich?
I thought I said I loved it. I said it a little bit.
Wow.
I didn't catch it though.
Oh god, I don't want to be braver here for a long time.
Give me a second psyche, I'll be right back and then Braden will go over here real quick.
I think she's asleep.
No.
This had to
Of course we're gonna hit for her so what did you do today? Thank you, thank you not much
You know, but I mean got some McDonald's I
Streamed a little bit when
Well, I got today a big Mac was a eight the most it was the big Mac a couple copies
fries
And I had this hey sassy
It's fortune it is fortune you but I got wheat I didn't get wheat tonight. I'll wheat tonight
Don't see my my bait it's around here some more
But I did get a vape and
Because I'm seeing okay here it is
They go to Marcy here. There we go. It's a mile high
So it means to eat the rest of this now smoke the rest of this I'll pass up soon 120 is sassy
Marcy Marcy new Kate
You guys are talking about her one time, you know, we're saying she had a morning show
I don't know what is transpired in the last week
I was trying to be cool with Kate and now she's like talking about my my father who passed away
I'm making fun of her for being dead. I don't know. That's what I heard
But that's what you heard or did you hear her say it or?
You hear it people were telling me that but
Directly
Yeah
Jamie said no
It's sad. Yeah, no, I know the people will do I know people will say these things
You haven't heard it, but it's all over the place
But you're all you're all the place. Yeah
That's a couple days
It's so fresh to you, so I know
Well, she actually she sent me condolences and so but
I didn't go on her. I was not gonna go on her show. I was just in chat just watching the other day
And she was just saying pretty some pretty terrible things about me like and I was like don't donate to him
You know, he'll spend it on meth and like
Well, that's what I'm saying. And I would never say, oh, don't donate to this person. Don't do it. So it's crazy.
Yeah
You know
Right I try to pull you down
I know but I mean it's like
With her and say other people saying, you know, I'm a bad person or
You know you have a genuine heart, you know, like you you have a playful nature to you as well
So I wouldn't trip too much on what other people think because their judgment
You doesn't change you, you know, it doesn't
It can't shake the core that you have. You know, you just gotta like unrubber your glue, bitch
You know what I mean? Like, I'm trying to fly above it. That's my advice. It's hard to do that.
Thank you.
I appreciate that.
And it's like, yeah, you think anybody says, you know, if I have to be alone, if I have to be like the only person to defend myself, if it comes down to me, all I can do is just love myself.
That's what I'll come down to. But I'd love to have people that love me and supported me around me.
I think you have a good group of people that love and support you.
It's difficult because of the way that the community is, you know?
And it's like split up and people are doing their little bullshit over here and bullshit over there and whatever, you know what I mean?
So, it's just, I don't know, it's hard.
You know, I can tell you it's hard. It's difficult having to talk about your situation, you know, whatever, you know, and past judgment, but
You gotta, you gotta learn how to like throw it off, you know, just like
Almost like you're wearing a cake, right? Like you're wearing your super hero face and it's like step to your back, right?
But like these people are talking shit and doing whatever you said, I like
Fly high, you know
Yeah
But you know, it's just one of those things
It's not easy. I can't I wish I had a solution first first I variable
But yeah, I wouldn't I don't worry too much about it. Like it's there's gonna be little things here and there
But I think I think from what I've seen hate like
Enjoyed you or enjoyed watching you at me. So
You know, I my perception could be off. I know it's been off a little bit lately, but
Yeah, I wasn't sure you're a good guy
And you run a good
You're funny about it. You're joking shit and that's fun
you know
Well, I knew that coming into this that coming on like putting my face out there like um, you know
Yeah, a lot of people don't feel pain
Hey sassy, hey mr. Pickett and I uh, yeah
Big good night. Give a few weird armorships away. Yeah, I just like the panel is like a little bit loud
and like everybody trying to like be funny and impress people and it's like it's like really like
i don't know i just feel like i got with it kicked in kicked out put in the pan i was trying
i'm trying different combinations but yeah i think you look but i mean i know like what what i'd
What people when something makes you uncomfortable you'll get intuition about when someone's trying to make fun of you and stuff like that
you'll get intuition
Marcy never did and
Page never did
Yeah
All right, I think just if it's other people that are telling you this, you haven't-
No, no, I- I actually saw that one where she was- because they played the clip or something.
I was like, LD and- because Amber had donated to the kickoff LD of the panel.
And he's like, oh, don't do anything to him.
Well, it's just Matt, he's just gonna spend it on math.
You know.
And whatever I change the gesture shoulders off baby, you know, it's gonna come you're gonna get the love and you're gonna get the hate
Judging you for one thing. I noticed that in your guys a community
There's a lot of tips for cat, you know where like someone says something or they don't like someone else
And so they try to persuade you not to like someone else
It's happening the same in our community, you know in the one-name pop watch community
you know, just even tonight, you know, you get to hear people that, you know, are Elias the
defense and whatever, TVP, and then there's the people that are chill, you know, it's because
they have pledge allegiance over there to the channel owner, but you just can't let that ego,
you know, work on that ego, trying to let that down and
If anything, my advice would be talk to Kate directly about it
Yeah, well, I haven't seen her in a lot of chat for a while
I don't I'm just trying to stick to my own chat and like I don't talk in other chats
Cuz I just get attacked in every chat I go to
You're gonna lease this chat. I can't go to Lisa's chat anymore. I just like people's are harassing
I can't send people to the channel anymore because people to harass her so I just like
I'll call it.
People need to block people, you know, like,
I know.
This is her chat.
In her chat, in her chat, people come over.
Yeah.
But I say, oh, the school releases, we release this channel.
And then people start saying terrible things like,
about me and like, and then, you know,
oh, so I can say, I just troll you or blah, blah, blah.
And so I can't.
Like I don't know and she I know she doesn't believe it and like you know, but
I don't want to bother anybody. I used to send people to people's chats and like
Try to help people's chats, but people just go in and say I'm trying to like troll the chat
So I can't do it anymore. So I'm not in chat anymore
Hey, they say they don't they don't know especially the smallest streamers and they they see me
And then people like oh look at this those weird guy
I get the weird thing that happens all the time between you and me because of my hair.
Well, you must know that it is labor.
Yeah, I don't know.
But, you know, like, this is one of those things.
So don't let that try to hold any bearing on who you are or affect you because you are,
from what I've seen, a genuine, fun, loving, and funny person.
Thank you.
For you two and
Yeah, I'm trying to have a lot more a lot more I think people were saying like I like ten people in the chat
But it could be the first hour or something. They were oh you like everybody's coming to you anymore and they move
Really aren't but it's still the people that are here like
Are like genuine people that I really care about and
And I'm sorry, like I try to you know how on the panels guys like
As I don't know I think I feel like if I just have a comfortable feeling about people were saying or like or someone
I just have to take them off and
Or I try different combinations of people
But I don't like if we made fun of my own show or like
You're filling it out. So, you know, there's gonna be some adjustment period, you know, yeah
Yeah, that's why I take this show seriously too because it's like this is like the first thing I've done in like years
that's actually like been successful and
like has so much potential and it's like good and it's like and so I don't like people messing with it and
Because it might be the only thing I have one day, you know, it's like if everything goes wrong in my life
This is something I did something that I
I still I'll still have and I'll still have that connection and remember my last connection
Yeah, so hope everyone's doing good tonight like
Is anyone in backstage here now?
No, I everyone no one's here. I'll probably improve it keep moving forward. If it's source of fun. I'm trying to
Yeah, see Mary Poppins, you know Mary Poppins, but
But I feel I believe that Mary Poppins energy where I feel like I'm gonna be here for a short time
I'm gonna help people as much as I can and like
This is Mary Poppins. She was here for like this that short time. She's the help and then
Yeah, and then she takes off in an umbrella and she's gone again
This is just a memory and somebody I'll just be memory, you know
And
Well, I saw I wanted to be a good memory. I want us all to have a happy memory that time
I was in say he's cat like that was just
Well, dude, we already you we already talk and I know some people I know I've told my mom some things that you know
We've been having fun and shit up here
But it's a good time, you know
It's pretty good. I think that you run a pretty good panel.
Thank you.
I don't know if my backstage people like it as much as you know, but what do I, what can
I say, you know, I haven't run a panel on my own in over a year. So when I got the next
surgery and all that shit, I was just like, I can't, I can't go back and look at any of
Crazy, but I can't believe I was running around with a broken book in it.
Well, you know, you're very strong to be able to like and you that's
Yeah, and you healed and you healed right yeah, yeah
And I know there's residual, you know, it's like, you know
Yeah, I gotta get my lower back fix like that. I have a broken screw in there
Don't ask me how I broke the screw. Maybe reverse cowboy in my hubby
like I don't know
They go lay in the bedroom
but um
Busted a titanium screw
Emma would always say um figure the body is like the meat soup she'd call it meats. Oh
And so
You know
Just think of it like, you know
Your body's like a car, you know, it's like and you know cars will literally break down, you know
So the human body will eventually break down, you know, it'll need repairs, sometimes there's
you know accidents and there's more extensive things, but it is really just the body. We're
not going to have this body forever. It's a very limited time compared to all the time that's ever
existed. We're just a little tiny little blip in time. And so I believe we have a consciousness.
It'll just look for the consciousness will look for a look for a body and that and so I think that's what the spiritual world is
Finding the right body for your consciousness to answer. Yeah
Yep, and also our life is probably pretty much
Our soul knows what it's getting into when we get when we go in this is not and it all all the soul one is experience and so
And once we're free from the human brain, like we'll be able to tap back into that
ageless time, you know, that is in our, that our soul has.
Yes.
Well, we're stuck in our human body, you know, because we're controlled by the brain.
Interesting.
That's why there's so much. Okay. Thank you, Marcy. What a great conversation though. Thank you
It was fun. I'm sorry. I'm sorry, but okay. Love you
I love you too. Have a good night. All right. Thank you
Bye chat
ma
Marcy's so cool. I love Marcy Marcy. Thank you so much Marcy
Wow, she's so cool guys
So wow
27 people in chat. You guys want to say anything to me?
I love
Hey, I have to hit it one more time. I'll pass it
But if you want to read me before I go
What's the talk about anything?
On the panel. I don't know as everyone got all of a sudden not so shy. He said big panel
Everyone's come on now. Everyone's like, oh
They don't hate you Jamie. Jamie. They hate me. They hate you. They hate you. They hate me
Okay, so people are just hateful so people are just hate just hate anything any little thing
Hey Morrissey, I love you Morrissey. Thanks for being the panel tonight.
It's fun having a show. We're even alone on the show right now, but all of it, all other guests.
People were like getting memberships and stuff.
so much love thank you so much and they hate i believe it's uh unresolved trauma with them
yeah and how about like how about i help how about anybody with trauma again i have i've been through
trauma and remember it's like if you don't feel like a hundred percent nobody feels a hundred percent
Erby, he has no wrench. Please. Oh, okay. I know it's gonna be now. It's gonna know he's gonna block Erby
I'm jamming because ears of ear mod
You know, you know the mother
But everyone's so quiet. You hate no one. I'd rather spend a little bit. Sometimes you speak up because nobody
Nobody very quiet. Yeah
I know
I hate no one either guys hate such
People are just going crazy
How about a drunk with you?
I'm gonna be a drunk with you.
I'm gonna be a drunk.
Hate, you're gonna hear this. I know Jamie, that's why, that's why, that's why
It's why I said do you want to be in a lot or not because they're gonna hate you if you support me.
You see?
Crazy energy, I know. That's what I want, what I want. Someone tell me the truth.
First person tell me the truth. I'll stress that person forever. I'm only going to
Cheers guys cheers queers
He's a strong word. Oh, hey, Nancy. We don't try to
Hey, you know either no, we don't want to hate anybody hate
You feel the passion, you feel pity, you want to help people, the best way for everyone.
I think we're everyone's happy, we're in a way that everyone's happy.
The thing is the world should be about making everyone happy as long as we can, because we
all will pass away.
There's been people Jamie keep the work. Yep. Jamie's awesome
You know, you know easy, you know
Hi, hi guys. How are you? I have one more drink. Hey guys, it's a pineapple
Coconut smash
Everyone's waiting for me to crash out some day
And we're gonna happen guys I mean, well, I mean I have several small crushes
Sorry my vision is blurry
Hey guys, why do you why do you why do you watch me? Why do you like me? Oh?
God and I'm the best time on the show
I'm sorry
I doubt the question about watching. Okay, you guys tell me what to say.
I'm sorry, guys, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come
Thank you. Well, it's always best everybody as a human being.
Okay, but I'm pretty serious.
Love you guys